(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[7],{318:function(e,t,n){var content=n(403);"string"==typeof content&&(content=[[e.i,content,""]]),content.locals&&(e.exports=content.locals);(0,n(6).default)("ef9a0bce",content,!0,{sourceMap:!1})},401:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/9e141ebc1c06d483bf85f4e5c8b3c7bc2d00ea2f.story","story_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.\\n\\nThe base, in southern Turkey near Syria, is a major resupply center for U.S. operations in Iraq and elsewhere in the Mideast and Asia.\\n\\nThe Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\\n\\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \\"genocide\\" label.\\n\\nThe House Foreign Affairs Committee last week adopted the nonbinding resolution. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi said she would bring the measure to a vote of the full House sometime next month. But the Bush administration urged Congress to drop the issue, and some leading Democrats urged Pelosi not to bring it to the floor.\\n\\nMajority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\\n\\n\\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \\"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\\"\\n\\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.\\n\\nAnd Democratic Reps. Alcee Hastings of Florida and John Tanner of Tennessee, both members of the U.S. House delegation to NATO, urged Pelosi to reconsider in a letter released Tuesday.\\n\\n\\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\\" they wrote.\\n\\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \\"a broad range of options\\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.\\n\\n\\"We\'re confident that we\'ll find ways to do that,\\" Ham told reporters at the Pentagon. \\"There\'s likely to be some increased cost and some other implications for that, and obviously we\'d prefer to maintain the access that we have.\\"\\n\\nDefense Secretary Robert Gates echoed lawmakers\' concerns last week.\\n\\n\\"About 70 percent of all air cargo going into Iraq goes through Turkey. ... About a third of the fuel that they consume goes through Turkey or comes from Turkey,\\" Gates said.\\n\\nHe also said that 95 percent of the Mine-Resistant Ambush-Protective vehicles, or MRAPs, being deployed in Iraq are flown through Turkey. The vehicles are built to withstand roadside bombs.  See Incirlik\'s key location »\\n\\nThe U.S. military issued a \\"warning order\\" a few days ago to ensure that alternative air crews, planes, fuel and routes are lined up if Turkey stops or restricts U.S. access to Incirlik, a source said.\\n\\nJordan and Kuwait are among the alternatives the United States is considering.\\n\\nSome fear pursuit of the resolution would also embolden the Turks to attack Kurdish rebels in northern Iraq which could further complicate Iraqi stability, U.S. officials said.\\n\\nIncirlik offers 10,000- and 9,000-foot runways and 57 hardened aircraft shelters, according Globalsecurity.org, a source of background information about military issues.\\n\\nGlobalsecurity said Incirlik has become a hub for cargo shipments to Iraq, taking over for Rhein-Main Air Base in Germany because it is closer to Iraq, reducing the strain on troops and aircraft. E-mail to a friend\\n\\nCNN\'s Barbara Starr and Deirdre Walsh contributed to this report.","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":870,"question":"Where is the key supply for the military?","answer_char_ranges":"411:429|482:523|3716:3725|686:691","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"3716:3725\\": 1, \\"411:429\\": 2}","para_text":"The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\\n\\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \\"genocide\\" label.","pred_ans":"incirlik","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":2603,"question":"turkey is upset by what?","answer_char_ranges":"307:351,354:377|116:152,154:167|None|330:351","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"116:152\\": 2}","para_text":"Defense Secretary Robert Gates echoed lawmakers\' concerns last week.\\n\\n\\"About 70 percent of all air cargo going into Iraq goes through Turkey. ... About a third of the fuel that they consume goes through Turkey or comes from Turkey,\\" Gates said.\\n\\nHe also said that 95 percent of the Mine-Resistant Ambush-Protective vehicles, or MRAPs, being deployed in Iraq are flown through Turkey. The vehicles are built to withstand roadside bombs.  See Incirlik\'s key location »","pred_ans":"about 70 percent of all air cargo going into iraq","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":7791,"question":"What is the genocide?","answer_char_ranges":"None|None","is_answer_absent":1,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"turkey \' s treatment of armenians in world war i","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":15263,"question":"What did the Majority Leader say?","answer_char_ranges":"1284:1311|1312:1380,1404:1473,1477:1598|1312:1380,1404:1473,1477:1598","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Majority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\\n\\n\\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \\"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\\"\\n\\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.","pred_ans":"i said i thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":19124,"question":"Which air base is Key for U.S. military\'s supply of Iraq mission?","answer_char_ranges":"193:202|1996:2005|1996:2005","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\\" they wrote.\\n\\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \\"a broad range of options\\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.","pred_ans":"incirlik air base","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":20186,"question":"Who is supplying the U.S. military?","answer_char_ranges":"618:631|2820:2829|504:511|193:211","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"2820:2829\\": 1, \\"618:631\\": 2}","para_text":"The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\\n\\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \\"genocide\\" label.","pred_ans":"turkey","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":20313,"question":"What air base is a key point of US military supply?","answer_char_ranges":"193:202|411:420|193:202","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\\" they wrote.\\n\\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \\"a broad range of options\\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.","pred_ans":"incirlik air base","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":20585,"question":"what is incirlik air base?","answer_char_ranges":"211:230|523:617|528:617|526:617","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"526:617\\": 1, \\"523:617\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"southern turkey","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":28645,"question":"What is the key point for U.S. military supply?","answer_char_ranges":"1996:2015|2274:2363|None|2044:2067,2071:2114,482:523,526:550,554:617","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"2071:2114\\": 1, \\"none\\": 1, \\"482:523\\": 1}","para_text":"The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\\n\\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \\"genocide\\" label.","pred_ans":"incirlik","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":38320,"question":"What does House resolution call killing of Armenians?","answer_char_ranges":"157:167|157:167","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"genocide","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":40579,"question":"What air base is a key point for US military supply?","answer_char_ranges":"193:202,214:230|1996:2005|193:202,411:420|1996:2005","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"193:202\\": 1, \\"none\\": 1, \\"1996:2005\\": 1}","para_text":"\\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\\" they wrote.\\n\\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \\"a broad range of options\\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.","pred_ans":"incirlik air base","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":46549,"question":"Which country is upset about World War 1 \\"genocide\\" resolution?","answer_char_ranges":"240:248,291:307|107:116|797:804|240:248","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"240:248\\": 1, \\"107:116\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"turkey","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":54946,"question":"Who is upset about genocide resolution?","answer_char_ranges":"240:248|25:35|240:248,291:300|None","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"240:248\\": 2, \\"none\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"democrats","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":55968,"question":"What air base is a key point for U.S. military supply of Iraq mission?","answer_char_ranges":"193:202|193:202","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\\" they wrote.\\n\\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \\"a broad range of options\\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.","pred_ans":"incirlik air base","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":56683,"question":"incirlik air base is the key point of who?","answer_char_ranges":"528:570|2057:2067,2071:2114|554:570|710:715","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"2071:2114\\": 1, \\"528:570\\": 1, \\"bad_question\\": 1}","para_text":"\\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\\" they wrote.\\n\\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \\"a broad range of options\\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.","pred_ans":"any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":62646,"question":"What are Dems doing?","answer_char_ranges":"107:167,48:107|25:98|None|107:167,35:107","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"35:107\\": 1, \\"25:98\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"some democrats appear to be wavering","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":70338,"question":"Who is upset about World War I \\"genocide\\" resolution in Congress?","answer_char_ranges":"1599:1680,1739:1890,1893:1920|240:248|1615:1628,1756:1771,1786:1798|25:35","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1599:1680\\": 2, \\"25:35\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"democrats","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":71079,"question":"Who is upset about genocide?","answer_char_ranges":"20:35|1250:1262,1615:1628,1756:1771,1786:1798|240:248,291:300,303:318|797:804","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"20:35\\": 1, \\"797:804\\": 1, \\"none\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"democrats","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":74100,"question":"What resolution is Turkey upset about?","answer_char_ranges":"81:87|116:152,154:167,81:87,98:107|116:152,154:167,98:107|330:377","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"330:377\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"the resolution calling the killing of armenians by ottoman turks genocide","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":79844,"question":"What did the House resolution call the killing of Armenians?","answer_char_ranges":"157:167|877:910|157:167","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"genocide","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":85554,"question":"what is turkey upset about?","answer_char_ranges":"116:152,154:167|303:377|300:318|287:377","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"303:377\\": 1, \\"300:318\\": 1, \\"116:152\\": 1}","para_text":"Defense Secretary Robert Gates echoed lawmakers\' concerns last week.\\n\\n\\"About 70 percent of all air cargo going into Iraq goes through Turkey. ... About a third of the fuel that they consume goes through Turkey or comes from Turkey,\\" Gates said.\\n\\nHe also said that 95 percent of the Mine-Resistant Ambush-Protective vehicles, or MRAPs, being deployed in Iraq are flown through Turkey. The vehicles are built to withstand roadside bombs.  See Incirlik\'s key location »","pred_ans":"about 70 percent of all air cargo going into iraq","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":88225,"question":"Who were the victims of the \\"genocide\\"?","answer_char_ranges":"129:139|129:154|833:843|341:351","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"129:139\\": 1, \\"833:843\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"armenians","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":88390,"question":"what did house resolution calls?","answer_char_ranges":"107:167|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"bad_question\\": 1, \\"107:167\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"genocide","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":89371,"question":"Who is upset about World War I genocide?","answer_char_ranges":"25:35|129:139|240:248|20:35","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2}","para_text":"The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\\n\\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \\"genocide\\" label.","pred_ans":"ankara","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":92067,"question":"Who is revisiting their positions?","answer_char_ranges":"1492:1511|1492:1511","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Majority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\\n\\n\\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \\"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\\"\\n\\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.","pred_ans":"a number of people who are revisiting their own positions","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":101022,"question":"what does the house resolution call genocide?","answer_char_ranges":"107:154|107:157|None|330:368","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"107:154\\": 1, \\"330:368\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"turkey \' s treatment of armenians in world war i","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":105077,"question":"Are Dems \\"revisiting their own positions?\\"","answer_char_ranges":"None|1482:1530,1540:1551","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1482:1530\\": 2}","para_text":"Majority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\\n\\n\\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \\"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\\"\\n\\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.","pred_ans":"there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":110258,"question":"Does House consider killing of Armenians \\"genocide?\\"","answer_char_ranges":"None|107:129,139:167,87:107","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey\'s treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\\n\\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\\n\\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.","pred_ans":"some democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious house resolution labeling turkey \' s treatment of armenians in world war i as genocide","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":110763,"question":"What air base is key for US military supply?","answer_char_ranges":"193:202|411:420|193:202","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\\" they wrote.\\n\\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \\"a broad range of options\\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.","pred_ans":"incirlik air base","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":117390,"question":"What says a number of Dems are revisiting?","answer_char_ranges":"1385:1404|1380:1404|1234:1262,1385:1404|1477:1494,1501:1519,1530:1551","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1385:1404\\": 1, \\"1234:1262\\": 1, \\"1530:1551\\": 1}","para_text":"Majority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\\n\\n\\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \\"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\\"\\n\\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.","pred_ans":"their own positions","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/5ba5e49e25610f42416b2e7ba76d7496acab0f78.story","story_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.\\n\\nProenza, 62, became the director in January after the retirement of Max Mayfield.\\n\\nProenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.\\n\\n\\"QuikSCAT is another tool that we use to forecast,\\" Lixion Avila said. \\"The forecast will not be degraded if we don\'t have the QuikSCAT.\\"\\n\\nLast week, the Commerce Department launched an unscheduled review of the hurricane center after word of the staff\'s dissatisfaction started to become public.\\n\\nHis staffers on Thursday issued a petition calling for him to step down.  Watch how Proenza lost the confidence of his staff »\\n\\nThe petition said the center\'s \\"effective functioning\\" is at stake as the Atlantic hurricane season heads toward its peak.\\n\\n\\"The undersigned staff ... has concluded that the center needs a new director, and with the heart of the hurricane season fast approaching, urges the Department of Commerce to make this happen as quickly as possible,\\" said the petition, which was signed by twenty-three people, including four of five senior hurricane specialists.\\n\\nHurricane center staffers told CNN\'s John Zarella they were unhappy not only about his comments about the QuikSCAT, but also about the environment at the center -- one characterized by closed doors and the public airing of dirty laundry.\\n\\nProenza on Friday told CNN he had contacted his superiors in Washington about \\"ways to move forward,\\" but added, \\"I am not going to resign.\\"\\n\\nProenza told CNN he did not think the staff should dictate the leadership through \\"signing petitions.\\"\\n\\nProenza graduated from Florida State University with a degree in meteorology. He began his career in tropical meteorology in the mid-1960s at NHC and as a meteorologist on the \\"hurricane hunter\\" aircraft, according to his biography posted on the agency\'s Web site.\\n\\nHe continued within the National Weather Service for more than 35 years, \\"receiving numerous performance commendations and awards, including recognition from the NWS Employees\' Organization as the NWS manager of the year for his collaborative leadership,\\" the bio said. E-mail to a friend","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":1390,"question":"What was signed asking him to leave","answer_char_ranges":"146:181|146:157|148:157|148:157","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"148:157\\": 2, \\"146:157\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"a petition","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":7280,"question":"What percentage of the NHC signed the petition?","answer_char_ranges":"None|110:122","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"110:122\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"nearly half","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":9640,"question":"WHO HAS LEFT THE NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTRE?","answer_char_ranges":"55:68|199:212,217:237,39:68,73:86|55:68","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"bill proenza","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":18864,"question":"What caused him to stop down?","answer_char_ranges":"129:181|110:181|104:181|627:668","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"104:181\\": 1, \\"bad_question\\": 1, \\"110:181\\": 1}","para_text":"Proenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.","pred_ans":"comments about a key hurricane satellite","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":24317,"question":"what is quickScat satellite?","answer_char_ranges":"648:658|648:658","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Proenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.","pred_ans":"five years beyond its life expectancy","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":29210,"question":"What was the staff unhappy about?","answer_char_ranges":"1443:1470,1653:1682|927:955,961:966|2022:2031,2037:2060,2066:2096|1497:1534","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"2037:2060\\": 1, \\"2066:2096\\": 1}","para_text":"Hurricane center staffers told CNN\'s John Zarella they were unhappy not only about his comments about the QuikSCAT, but also about the environment at the center -- one characterized by closed doors and the public airing of dirty laundry.\\n\\nProenza on Friday told CNN he had contacted his superiors in Washington about \\"ways to move forward,\\" but added, \\"I am not going to resign.\\"\\n\\nProenza told CNN he did not think the staff should dictate the leadership through \\"signing petitions.\\"","pred_ans":"the environment at the center","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":40939,"question":"Who is the National Hurricane Center director?","answer_char_ranges":"55:68|55:68","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"bill proenza","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":42069,"question":"What position did Bill Proenze hold?","answer_char_ranges":"20:55|20:46|20:55","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"national hurricane center director","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":44627,"question":"What did Proenza came under fire for?","answer_char_ranges":"627:685,787:874|627:685|627:636|594:685,883:910,914:927","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"627:685\\": 2, \\"627:636\\": 1}","para_text":"Proenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.","pred_ans":"comments about a key hurricane satellite called quikscat","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":54504,"question":"What size part of the NHC signed the petition?","answer_char_ranges":"110:122|1860:1873|1860:1881|117:129","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"117:129\\": 2, \\"110:122\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"nearly half","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":55214,"question":"What was the petition for","answer_char_ranges":"157:165,169:181|1394:1402,1406:1424|133:148,157:165,169:181,55:68|46:86","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"169:181\\": 2}","para_text":"Last week, the Commerce Department launched an unscheduled review of the hurricane center after word of the staff\'s dissatisfaction started to become public.\\n\\nHis staffers on Thursday issued a petition calling for him to step down.  Watch how Proenza lost the confidence of his staff »\\n\\nThe petition said the center\'s \\"effective functioning\\" is at stake as the Atlantic hurricane season heads toward its peak.","pred_ans":"calling for him to step down","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":58068,"question":"what were staff unhappy with?","answer_char_ranges":"2003:2037,2041:2051,2055:2096|2018:2051,2066:2096|779:798,803:874|1985:1990,2003:2096,2099:2173","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"2066:2096\\": 1, \\"2003:2096\\": 2}","para_text":"Hurricane center staffers told CNN\'s John Zarella they were unhappy not only about his comments about the QuikSCAT, but also about the environment at the center -- one characterized by closed doors and the public airing of dirty laundry.\\n\\nProenza on Friday told CNN he had contacted his superiors in Washington about \\"ways to move forward,\\" but added, \\"I am not going to resign.\\"\\n\\nProenza told CNN he did not think the staff should dictate the leadership through \\"signing petitions.\\"","pred_ans":"the environment at the center","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":58681,"question":"what did proenza come under fire for?","answer_char_ranges":"627:685|622:685|627:685","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Proenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.","pred_ans":"comments about a key hurricane satellite called quikscat","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":61704,"question":"What are the staff unhappy about?","answer_char_ranges":"2018:2031,2037:2060,2066:2096,2099:2173|2018:2031,2037:2060,2066:2096|2018:2031,2037:2051,2066:2082|2022:2031,2037:2051,2070:2096","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"2018:2031\\": 2}","para_text":"Hurricane center staffers told CNN\'s John Zarella they were unhappy not only about his comments about the QuikSCAT, but also about the environment at the center -- one characterized by closed doors and the public airing of dirty laundry.\\n\\nProenza on Friday told CNN he had contacted his superiors in Washington about \\"ways to move forward,\\" but added, \\"I am not going to resign.\\"\\n\\nProenza told CNN he did not think the staff should dictate the leadership through \\"signing petitions.\\"","pred_ans":"the environment at the center","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":63727,"question":"What does NHC mean?","answer_char_ranges":"20:46|20:46","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"national oceanic and atmospheric administration","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":67051,"question":"What is the NHC petition for?","answer_char_ranges":"157:165,169:181|157:165,169:181","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"ouster","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":67398,"question":"who is national hurricane center director?","answer_char_ranges":"55:68|55:68","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"bill proenza","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":70384,"question":"What organisation did Bill Proenza work for?","answer_char_ranges":"20:46|20:46","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"national oceanic and atmospheric administration","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":73291,"question":"What did NHC sign a petition for?","answer_char_ranges":"169:181|157:181|1394:1402,1406:1424|1406:1424","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"157:181\\": 1, \\"1406:1424\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"his ouster","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":79500,"question":"Who made comments about the QuikSCAT satellite?","answer_char_ranges":"586:627,642:658,668:675|1017:1027,586:594|450:463|586:594","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"586:594\\": 2}","para_text":"Proenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.","pred_ans":"proenza","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":80893,"question":"What has Proenza been criticized for?","answer_char_ranges":"627:685|594:611,622:668,675:685,702:720,724:740,812:828,837:848,862:874|627:685","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Proenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.","pred_ans":"comments about a key hurricane satellite called quikscat","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":82078,"question":"Who signed a petition?","answer_char_ranges":"129:139|1435:1443|110:139,146:148,1857:1881|117:139","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"117:139\\": 1, \\"110:139\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"nearly half of the nhc staff","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":85727,"question":"Is the NHC staff happy?","answer_char_ranges":"None|2012:2096,2103:2117,2120:2133,2141:2173","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"nearly half of the nhc staff signed a petition calling for his ouster","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":88147,"question":"What comments dud he make","answer_char_ranges":"927:966|644:874|675:685,702:740|927:966","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"927:966\\": 1, \\"bad_question\\": 1, \\"644:874\\": 1}","para_text":"Proenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.","pred_ans":"proenza said if it were to fail , forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent . he said washington reprimanded him for the remarks : \\" they wanted me to be quiet about it . \\"","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":88271,"question":"What is the name of the satelite","answer_char_ranges":"675:685|675:685","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"national oceanic and atmospheric administration","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":96046,"question":"What did Proenza cone under fire for?","answer_char_ranges":"594:685|594:685","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Proenza caused an uproar last month with comments about a key hurricane satellite called QuikSCAT. The satellite is five years beyond its life expectancy and operating on a backup transmitter. Proenza said if it were to fail, forecast tracks could be thrown off by as much as 16 percent.\\n\\nHe said Washington reprimanded him for the remarks: \\"They wanted me to be quiet about it.\\"\\n\\nBut one of the center\'s longtime forecasters said Proenza\'s comments were misguided.","pred_ans":"comments about a key hurricane satellite called quikscat","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":96346,"question":"Which company was Bill Proenza director of?","answer_char_ranges":"20:46|20:46","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"national hurricane center","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":104730,"question":"Who was unhappy with him?","answer_char_ranges":"117:139|1207:1227|1935:1961|1351:1364","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"117:139\\": 1, \\"1935:1961\\": 1, \\"1351:1364\\": 1}","para_text":"Hurricane center staffers told CNN\'s John Zarella they were unhappy not only about his comments about the QuikSCAT, but also about the environment at the center -- one characterized by closed doors and the public airing of dirty laundry.\\n\\nProenza on Friday told CNN he had contacted his superiors in Washington about \\"ways to move forward,\\" but added, \\"I am not going to resign.\\"\\n\\nProenza told CNN he did not think the staff should dictate the leadership through \\"signing petitions.\\"","pred_ans":"hurricane center staffers","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":110230,"question":"Who left their position at the National Hurricane Center","answer_char_ranges":"55:68|55:68","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"bill proenza","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":114316,"question":"What did bill proenza do","answer_char_ranges":"212:225|68:86|594:611,622:642,644:668,675:685,812:828,837:848,862:874|627:685","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"68:86\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- National Hurricane Center director Bill Proenza left his position Monday, just days after nearly half of the NHC staff signed a petition calling for his ouster.\\n\\nHurricane Center Bill Proenza left his job as director Monday.\\n\\nProenza is still employed by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration -- a parent organization of the NHC --  but he is currently on leave, said NOAA spokesman Anson Franklin.\\n\\nDeputy Director Ed Rappaport has been temporarily placed in charge.","pred_ans":"left his position monday , just days after nearly half of the nhc staff signed a petition calling for his ouster . hurricane center bill proenza left his job as director monday","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/35f0e33de7923036a97ac245d899f990bda5e242.story","story_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.\\n\\nThe president\'s doctor had recommended a repeat procedure in about five years.\\n\\nThe procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\\n\\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.\\n\\nSnow himself is undergoing chemotherapy for cancer that began in his colon and spread to his liver.\\n\\nSnow told reporters he had a chemo session scheduled later Friday.  Watch Snow talk about Bush\'s procedure and his own colon cancer »\\n\\n\\"The president wants to encourage everybody to use surveillance,\\" Snow said.\\n\\nThe American Cancer Society recommends that people without high-risk factors or symptoms begin getting screened for signs of colorectal cancer at age 50. E-mail to a friend","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":2871,"question":"Who will his powers be transferred to?","answer_char_ranges":"35:47|20:47|20:47","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"vice president dick cheney","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":5674,"question":"think there will be problems now?","answer_char_ranges":"None|None","is_answer_absent":1,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"no abnormalities were found","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":5796,"question":"What medical procedure will Bush have on Saturday?","answer_char_ranges":"138:159|138:159","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"colonoscopy","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":12657,"question":"What procedure is he having?","answer_char_ranges":"138:159|146:159|138:159","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"The procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\\n\\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.","pred_ans":"colonoscopy","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":12772,"question":"What happens to his powers while he is anesthetized?","answer_char_ranges":"20:78|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"20:78\\": 2, \\"none\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"vice president dick cheney will serve as acting president briefly saturday","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":13404,"question":"What is the date of the Saturday that President Bush will have a routine colonoscopy?","answer_char_ranges":"None|None","is_answer_absent":1,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"friday","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":15435,"question":"When did he last have a colonoscopy?","answer_char_ranges":"386:397|386:397","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"june 2002","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":20080,"question":"Who will have a routine colonoscopy?","answer_char_ranges":"101:116|101:116","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"president bush","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":32066,"question":"What problems were found in 2002 exam?","answer_char_ranges":"401:418|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"401:418\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"no abnormalities","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":38260,"question":"When did he last have this procedure?","answer_char_ranges":"386:397|386:397","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"june 2002","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":39388,"question":"What was the date in 2002 when Bush had his last colonoscopy, which found no problems?","answer_char_ranges":"386:391|386:391","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"june","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":42988,"question":"is bush\'s colon healthy?","answer_char_ranges":"401:430|446:521|362:397,401:430|401:430","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"401:430\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"no abnormalities were found","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":50237,"question":"Who is in charge while the president is anesthetized?","answer_char_ranges":"20:25,35:47|111:116,20:25,35:68,78:95|111:116,20:25,35:68,78:95","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"dick cheney","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":52652,"question":"Who will be granted presidential power while Bush is anesthetized?","answer_char_ranges":"20:47|20:47,52:78|101:111,20:47,52:95|20:47,52:78","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"20:47\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"vice president dick cheney","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":63451,"question":"When was Bush\'s last colonoscopy?","answer_char_ranges":"386:397|386:397","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"june 2002","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":82170,"question":"What kind of exam is Bush having?","answer_char_ranges":"146:159|367:379|146:159","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":84781,"question":"when he\'s asleep are his powers transferred as well?","answer_char_ranges":"101:132,35:78,95:101|20:78|101:132,20:78,95:101|None","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"20:78\\": 1, \\"35:78\\": 1, \\"bad_question\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"vice president dick cheney will serve as acting president briefly saturday while president bush","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":85165,"question":"What person  will be presidentwhen Bush is anesthtized?","answer_char_ranges":"20:47|35:47|None|20:47","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"20:47\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"dick cheney","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":87304,"question":"What will President Bush have on Saturday?","answer_char_ranges":"138:159|119:159|136:159|136:159","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"136:159\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"a routine colonoscopy","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":92880,"question":"Where will his powers be transferred?","answer_char_ranges":"20:47|25:35,321:333|None|20:47","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"321:333\\": 1, \\"20:47\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"camp david , maryland","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":93980,"question":"Who will be in charge while he\'s undergoing the procedure?","answer_char_ranges":"35:47|20:47|20:47","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"The procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\\n\\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.","pred_ans":"dr . richard tubb","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":94172,"question":"What will President Bush have?","answer_char_ranges":"138:159|146:159|138:159","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"a routine colonoscopy","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":105493,"question":"What procedure is President Bush having?","answer_char_ranges":"None|146:159","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"146:159\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"colonoscopy","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":109063,"question":"Who had a colonoscopy in 2002?","answer_char_ranges":"None|101:116|101:146","is_answer_absent":0.333333333333,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"101:146\\": 1, \\"101:116\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"president bush","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":113125,"question":"who will have the president\'s powers when he is anesthetized?","answer_char_ranges":"35:47|20:25,35:47|20:25,35:47","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"vice president dick cheney","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":116915,"question":"What is the reason why the President\'s powers will be transferred to the vice president?","answer_char_ranges":"119:159|138:159|111:116,119:159|119:159","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"119:159\\": 2, \\"138:159\\": 1}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"president bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":117663,"question":"what procedure will president bush have?","answer_char_ranges":"138:159|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"138:159\\": 2}","para_text":"WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\\n\\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\\n\\nBush\'s last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.","pred_ans":"colonoscopy","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/d256aee1a47eb5b489dee6fb72ab7f7d1483a37f.story","story_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, the ruling coalition\'s 72-year-old nominee for the mainly ceremonial post, easily beat opposition-backed challenger and vice president, Bhairon Singh Shekhawat, in a vote by the national parliament and state politicians.\\n\\n\\"This a victory of the people,\\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \\"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\\"\\n\\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.\\n\\nThe governor of the northwestern desert state of Rajasthan, she emerged on the national stage when the Congress-led coalition and its communist allies failed to agree on a joint candidate.\\n\\n\\"This is a very special moment for us women, and men of course, in our country because for the first time we have a woman being elected president of India,\\" Congress party leader Sonia Gandhi, India\'s most powerful politician, said.\\n\\nSupporters hoped Patil\'s candidacy would help bring issues that plague women in India, like dowry-related violence, into the public spotlight. A woman is murdered, raped or abused every three minutes on average in India.\\n\\nHer presidency also reflects the growing power of some women in India, where an increasing number are taking part in the workforce and in schools and hold senior positions in corporations.\\n\\nAfter the results, Patil supporters took to the streets, singing and dancing as others lit fire crackers and beat large brass drums.\\n\\nIndia has had a number of female icons in the past -- most famously Sonia Gandhi\'s mother-in-law, Indira, who was one of the world\'s first female prime ministers in 1966.\\n\\nBut hope Patil\'s presidency would spark only positive talk about women\'s influence in India evaporated when it emerged the bank for women she helped established was closed in 2003 because of bad debts and amid accusations of financial irregularities.\\n\\nThe employees\' union has taken Patil and others to court, claiming loans meant for poor women were instead given to her brother and other relatives and not returned. She was also accused of trying to shield her brother in a murder inquiry.\\n\\nPrime Minister Manmohan Singh, who has dismissed accusations against her as \\"mud-slinging\\", said on Saturday her victory was \\"a vote against the politics of divisiveness\\".\\n\\n\\"All the allegations against me are motivated and have already been answered,\\" Patil said in a statement last week.\\n\\nHer campaign was marked by other mishaps as well.\\n\\nShe managed to offend many minority Muslims, and anger some historians, by saying Indian women first veiled their heads as protection against 16th century Muslim invaders.\\n\\nThen she dismayed modern India by claiming she had experienced a \\"divine premonition\\" that she was destined for higher office from a long dead spiritual guru.\\n\\nCritics also dug up a comment she was said to have made as Maharashtra\'s health minister in 1975, saying people with hereditary diseases should be sterilized. E-mail to a friend","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":13910,"question":"What happened during the election?","answer_char_ranges":"40:76|52:76|233:296|None","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"233:296\\": 1, \\"52:76\\": 1, \\"40:76\\": 1}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"scandal","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":17930,"question":"What is the victory being called?","answer_char_ranges":"551:567|551:567","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"This a victory of the people,\\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \\"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\\"\\n\\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.","pred_ans":"victory of the people","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":21550,"question":"Who was was the ruling coalition\'s nominee?","answer_char_ranges":"297:317|297:313|297:313","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"This a victory of the people,\\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \\"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\\"\\n\\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.","pred_ans":"patil","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":21551,"question":"Who\'s supporters are calling the victory a boost for women\'s rights?","answer_char_ranges":"233:249,30:36|297:313|233:249|233:249","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"233:249\\": 2}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":23582,"question":"Who was the coalition\'s nominee?","answer_char_ranges":"297:313|297:313","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"This a victory of the people,\\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \\"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\\"\\n\\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.","pred_ans":"patil","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":26782,"question":"who cares about womens rights?","answer_char_ranges":"30:36|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"30:36\\": 2}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":33599,"question":"Which country elected it\'s first female president?","answer_char_ranges":"1266:1274,256:264|30:36|30:36","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"india","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":36292,"question":"What nation elected their first female president?","answer_char_ranges":"256:264|30:36|30:36","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"india","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":38565,"question":"Whom did India elect president?","answer_char_ranges":"233:249|233:249","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"pratibha patil","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":40713,"question":"What age is the new president?","answer_char_ranges":"249:253|233:253|249:253","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"72","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":44704,"question":"What is Patil\'s age?","answer_char_ranges":"249:253|249:253","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"This a victory of the people,\\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \\"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\\"\\n\\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.","pred_ans":"what is patil \' s age ? [SEP] \\" this a victory of the people , \\" patil told reporters after official results were announced saturday","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":45836,"question":"Who did India elect as the first female president on Saturday?","answer_char_ranges":"233:264,270:278|233:249|233:249","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"pratibha patil","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":47249,"question":"What was marked by scandal?","answer_char_ranges":"204:213|195:213|195:213","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"a bitter campaign","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":47433,"question":"What kind of election campaign was it?","answer_char_ranges":"197:204|195:204|2638:2654|197:204","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"197:204\\": 2, \\"2638:2654\\": 1}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"bitter","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":50775,"question":"What age was Patil at the time of the election?","answer_char_ranges":"336:348|249:253|249:253","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"This is a very special moment for us women, and men of course, in our country because for the first time we have a woman being elected president of India,\\" Congress party leader Sonia Gandhi, India\'s most powerful politician, said.\\n\\nSupporters hoped Patil\'s candidacy would help bring issues that plague women in India, like dowry-related violence, into the public spotlight. A woman is murdered, raped or abused every three minutes on average in India.","pred_ans":"what age was patil at the time of the election ? [SEP] \\" this is a very special moment for us women , and men of course , in our country because for the first time we have a woman","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":56858,"question":"What is the name of the president elect?","answer_char_ranges":"233:249|233:249","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"pratibha patil","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":59196,"question":"is a female president a good idea?","answer_char_ranges":"1128:1148,1212:1253,1263:1274,1351:1438|132:153,156:165,168:187|None|2852:2902,3258:3266,3287:3292,3295:3325","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2, \\"132:153\\": 1}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":61756,"question":"what was the scandal?","answer_char_ranges":"195:213|2192:2230,2234:2249,2388:2449,2985:3011,3017:3023,3026:3075|2192:2230,2234:2320|30:76","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"30:76\\": 1, \\"2388:2449\\": 2}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"a bitter campaign","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":63113,"question":"What is her name?","answer_char_ranges":"233:249|233:249","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"pratibha patil","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":63412,"question":"What is Patil\'s first name?","answer_char_ranges":"233:242|233:242","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"pratibha","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":81024,"question":"Who was the first female president of India?","answer_char_ranges":"233:249|233:249","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"pratibha patil","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":83310,"question":"what was the election campaign marked by?","answer_char_ranges":"223:232|223:232","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"scandal","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":85451,"question":"What is the age of President Elect Patil?","answer_char_ranges":"249:253|336:348|249:253","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"72","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":88880,"question":"What are the reasons that Pratibha Patil\'s supporters are calling her victory a boost for women\'s rights?","answer_char_ranges":"1397:1410,1415:1467|1386:1410,1415:1494|256:296|30:76","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1415:1494\\": 1, \\"256:296\\": 1, \\"30:76\\": 1}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"millions of downtrodden women , despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":90048,"question":"what is a bppst for women\'s rights?","answer_char_ranges":"None|48:76","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":94789,"question":"Who is the president of India?","answer_char_ranges":"233:249|233:249","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"pratibha patil","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":109001,"question":"What number of female presidents have been elected?","answer_char_ranges":"264:270|52:58|48:58|264:270","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"48:58\\": 1, \\"none\\": 1, \\"52:58\\": 1}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"72","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":110753,"question":"who is india\'s first female president?","answer_char_ranges":"233:249|233:249","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"pratibha patil","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":112643,"question":"What are the reasons that the bitter election campaign was marked by scandal?","answer_char_ranges":"2188:2230,2234:2320,2321:2491,2495:2561|2388:2394,2400:2420,2428:2449|2260:2320,2487:2561|2188:2230,2234:2320,2388:2487,2511:2561,2918:2948,2952:2975,3085:3107,3334:3395","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"2511:2561\\": 1, \\"2260:2320\\": 1}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":118293,"question":"Was the election campaign marked by scandal?","answer_char_ranges":"195:232|195:204","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"195:232\\": 2}","para_text":"NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\\n\\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India\'s first elected female president.","pred_ans":"a bitter campaign marked by scandal","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/e3dd06d326c8d53722bdc5c8428e29c68a60d0d5.story","story_text":"(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family\'s \\"lives were just changed forever\\" by the tragedy.\\n\\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\\n\\n\\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\\" he said.\\n\\nAuman said the situation was \\"hard to fathom.\\"\\n\\n\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.\\n\\nSix other South Carolina students were able to get out of the house in time. The six were treated and released from nearby Brunswick Community Hospital, but Auman\'s daughter was hospitalized again in Hartsville, South Carolina.\\n\\nAuthorities from the state Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives are leading the investigation into the cause of the fire.\\n\\nOcean Isle Beach Mayor Debbie Smith said the house was \\"engulfed\\" in flames when the fire department arrived on the scene, about five minutes after being notified. The flames shot into the sky and ultimately left little more than portions of the framing.\\n\\nFire officials do not believe foul play was involved.  Watch a neighbor\'s video, fears of fast-burning fire »\\n\\nDennis A. Pruitt, the vice president for student affairs for the University of South Carolina, said investigators have said it would be Tuesday or Wednesday before the identities of the victims are confirmed publicly.\\n\\nIt could be as much as a month until investigators know the cause of the fire, Pruitt said.\\n\\nThe university did not cancel classes on Monday, but Pruitt said arrangements had been made for those who need to go home or stay out of class at the 28,000-student campus.\\n\\nPruitt said meetings had been held Sunday with members of Delta Delta Delta sorority and Sigma Alpha Epsilon fraternity. The South Carolina students were affiliated with those houses, he said, although he stressed that the weekend was not an official Greek function.\\n\\nHe also said counselors and ministers were available to help students deal with the loss of their classmates.\\n\\nThe university president, Dr. Andrew Sorenson, contacted the families of those who died in the fire to express the condolences and support of the university community.\\n\\nJay Laura, student president of the USC chapter of Sigma Alpha Epsilon, said the campus would pull together after the tragedy.\\n\\n\\"If any place can come together to help in the healing process and the aftermath of an event like this, it is South Carolina,\\" Laura said at a Monday afternoon press conference.\\n\\nFire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.\\n\\n\\"The smoke was pouring out, couldn\'t really breathe, so I had to make a quick decision. [I] just kind of leaned out the window and luckily I jumped far enough to make it into the canal.\\"\\n\\nNeighbors flocked to see the fire as firefighters battled and ultimately got the blaze under control.  See the scenes of devastation »\\n\\nGeorge Smith, who lives across the street from the house, said he heard sirens between 6:30 and 7 a.m. and went outside to see \\"the whole sky lit up.\\"\\n\\n\\"The whole house was completely engulfed in flames, up to about 20 feet,\\" he said. \\"I have never seen [a fire] move so fast.\\"\\n\\nGeorge Smith said the house\'s occupants were \\"partying in there yesterday and into the night.\\" After about 10:30 p.m. Saturday they quieted down, he said.\\n\\nLinda Sing said she was walking her dog when she saw the fiery destruction. She noted that firefighters had saved an adjacent house by spraying it down with water.\\n\\n\\"We knew there were people in there, but we hoped and prayed they\'d gotten out,\\" Sing said. \\"This is the worst thing I\'ve ever seen. We\'ve had hurricanes, but this is worse.\\"\\n\\nOcean Isle Beach is a popular resort destination along North Carolina\'s southern coast. The year-round population of the 7-mile-long island is about 425, but it swells to about 25,000 during the summer season, according to the town\'s Web site. E-mail to a friend","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":1623,"question":"Who  among six survivors hospitalized?","answer_char_ranges":"184:225|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"184:225\\": 2}","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"university of south carolina students and a clemson university student","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":6689,"question":"Whose daughter was hospitalized?","answer_char_ranges":"184:195|184:195","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family\'s \\"lives were just changed forever\\" by the tragedy.\\n\\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\\n\\n\\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\\" he said.","pred_ans":"chip auman","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":14864,"question":"what was the amount of suvivors?","answer_char_ranges":"None|925:929","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"925:929\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family\'s \\"lives were just changed forever\\" by the tragedy.\\n\\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\\n\\n\\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\\" he said.","pred_ans":"seven","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":16808,"question":"From which university were the six dead students?","answer_char_ranges":"789:807|792:798,822:830|789:807","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"university of south carolina","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":17334,"question":"What happened to the house owner\'s daughter?","answer_char_ranges":"247:264|225:288|225:336|225:264","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"225:264\\": 2, \\"225:288\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family\'s \\"lives were just changed forever\\" by the tragedy.\\n\\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\\n\\n\\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\\" he said.","pred_ans":"hospitalized and in stable condition","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":17456,"question":"University of South Carolina mourns deaths of six students","answer_char_ranges":"None|None","is_answer_absent":1,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"six university of south carolina students and a clemson university student died in the fire early sunday morning in ocean isle beach , north carolina .","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":19200,"question":"Where did the man jump into?","answer_char_ranges":"3126:3150,3155:3163|3157:3163|3155:3163|3155:3163","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"3155:3163\\": 2}","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"a canal","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":22683,"question":"Who jumped in a canal?","answer_char_ranges":"3054:3067|3054:3067","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"tripp wylie","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":23652,"question":"What story did the survivor jump from?","answer_char_ranges":"3131:3150|3131:3143|3131:3143","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"third - story window","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":27579,"question":"What was the house owner\'s daughter?","answer_char_ranges":"204:216|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"204:216\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family\'s \\"lives were just changed forever\\" by the tragedy.\\n\\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\\n\\n\\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\\" he said.","pred_ans":"18 - year - old","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":35961,"question":"What was the number of survivors hospitalized?","answer_char_ranges":"1006:1010|1002:1078,925:1002|1006:1010,1015:1023,1027:1036,1068:1078,925:929,950:1002|57:63","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1006:1010\\": 2, \\"925:929\\": 1}","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"six","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":39305,"question":"Who mourns death of six students?","answer_char_ranges":"184:195|736:757|736:765|929:935","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"736:765\\": 1, \\"184:195\\": 1, \\"736:757\\": 1}","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"two college campuses","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":43238,"question":"which was the cause of death of the 6 students?","answer_char_ranges":"98:103|861:866|861:866","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Authorities from the state Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives are leading the investigation into the cause of the fire.\\n\\nOcean Isle Beach Mayor Debbie Smith said the house was \\"engulfed\\" in flames when the fire department arrived on the scene, about five minutes after being notified. The flames shot into the sky and ultimately left little more than portions of the framing.","pred_ans":"fire","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":44628,"question":"because I try out a survivor?","answer_char_ranges":"3040:3045|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"bad_question\\": 2}","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"jumped out of a third - story window into a canal to escape the flames","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":58111,"question":"Who was hospitalized?","answer_char_ranges":"184:195,204:225|184:225|1082:1099,204:225|184:195,204:225","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1082:1099\\": 1, \\"184:225\\": 1, \\"204:225\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family\'s \\"lives were just changed forever\\" by the tragedy.\\n\\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\\n\\n\\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\\" he said.","pred_ans":"his 18 - year - old daughter","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":67856,"question":"One survivor jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape","answer_char_ranges":"3054:3067|3060:3067,3069:3107|238:243,98:103|1082:1099","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"bad_question\\": 2}","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"tripp wylie","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":74554,"question":"Who mourned the deaths?","answer_char_ranges":"736:757|736:757","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"two college campuses","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":76164,"question":"Where did one survivor jump to?","answer_char_ranges":"3150:3163|3558:3566|3150:3163","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"a canal","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":78654,"question":"which university mourns deaths of six students?","answer_char_ranges":"789:807|792:807,822:830|789:807","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"university of south carolina","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":79887,"question":"\\"Heartbroken\\" house owner\'s daughter among six survivors hospitalized","answer_char_ranges":"None|225:238,243:247","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"bad_question\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family\'s \\"lives were just changed forever\\" by the tragedy.\\n\\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\\n\\n\\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\\" he said.","pred_ans":"chip auman said his 18 - year - old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":84615,"question":"Who mourns the students?","answer_char_ranges":"None|13:19,184:195,19:51,9:13","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2, \\"184:195\\": 2}","para_text":"He also said counselors and ministers were available to help students deal with the loss of their classmates.\\n\\nThe university president, Dr. Andrew Sorenson, contacted the families of those who died in the fire to express the condolences and support of the university community.\\n\\nJay Laura, student president of the USC chapter of Sigma Alpha Epsilon, said the campus would pull together after the tragedy.","pred_ans":"the university community","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":85350,"question":"where they are hospitalized survivors?","answer_char_ranges":"1125:1153|1048:1078|1125:1153","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"two college campuses mourned monday . six university of south carolina students and a clemson university student died in the fire early sunday morning in ocean isle beach , north carolina","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":85558,"question":"Where did one survivor jump?","answer_char_ranges":"3107:3235|3131:3163|3122:3163|3122:3163","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"3122:3163\\": 1, \\"none\\": 1, \\"3131:3163\\": 1}","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"a canal","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":85896,"question":"What did the University mourn?","answer_char_ranges":"57:85|2637:2664|57:80|774:778,789:830,841:866","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"57:85\\": 1, \\"57:80\\": 2}","para_text":"He also said counselors and ministers were available to help students deal with the loss of their classmates.\\n\\nThe university president, Dr. Andrew Sorenson, contacted the families of those who died in the fire to express the condolences and support of the university community.\\n\\nJay Laura, student president of the USC chapter of Sigma Alpha Epsilon, said the campus would pull together after the tragedy.","pred_ans":"those who died in the fire","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":88843,"question":"Who mourns deaths of six students?","answer_char_ranges":"13:51,736:765,9:13|736:757|736:757","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"two college campuses","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":95405,"question":"What school did the students go to?","answer_char_ranges":"778:807,822:841|792:807,822:841|778:807,816:820,822:841|778:807,822:841","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"778:807\\": 2}","para_text":"Dennis A. Pruitt, the vice president for student affairs for the University of South Carolina, said investigators have said it would be Tuesday or Wednesday before the identities of the victims are confirmed publicly.\\n\\nIt could be as much as a month until investigators know the cause of the fire, Pruitt said.\\n\\nThe university did not cancel classes on Monday, but Pruitt said arrangements had been made for those who need to go home or stay out of class at the 28,000-student campus.","pred_ans":"university of south carolina","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":97466,"question":"Who  jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape?","answer_char_ranges":"3054:3067|3054:3067","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"tripp wylie","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":115145,"question":"What number of survivors were hospitalized?","answer_char_ranges":"None|1002:1010,1015:1078","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1002:1010\\": 2}","para_text":"\\"There\'s just no words to describe what we\'ve been going through,\\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \\"We\'re numb, we\'re confused, we\'re heartbroken.\\"\\n\\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\\n\\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.","pred_ans":"six","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":115962,"question":"who jum p imto a canal to escape?","answer_char_ranges":"3054:3067|3054:3067","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"tripp wylie","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":117291,"question":"Where did the survivor land when escaping?","answer_char_ranges":"3131:3150|3549:3566|3157:3163|3157:3163","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"3549:3566\\": 2}","para_text":"Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\\n\\n\\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.","pred_ans":"a canal","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/cac7a712935380d74410a7cba8d406235d51249a.story","story_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.\\n\\nSpidey then gave the boy from a far-away land a gentle hug, embracing him in his iconic blue and red tights. He showed Youssif a few tricks, like how to shoot a web from his wrist. Only this time, no web was spun.\\n\\n\\"All right Youssif!\\" Spider-Man said after the boy mimicked his wrist movement.\\n\\nOther superheroes crowded around to get a closer look. Even the Green Goblin stopped his villainous ways to tell the boy hi. Youssif remained unfazed. He didn\'t take a liking to Spider-Man\'s nemesis.\\n\\nSpidey was just too cool.\\n\\n\\"It was my favorite thing,\\" the boy said later. \\"I want to see him again.\\"\\n\\nHe then felt compelled to add: \\"I know it\'s not the real Spider-Man.\\"\\n\\nThis was the day of dreams when the boy\'s nightmares were, at least temporarily, forgotten. He met SpongeBob, Lassie and a 3-year-old orangutan named Archie. The hairy, brownish-red primate took to the boy, grabbing his hand and holding it. Even when Youssif pulled away, Archie would inch his hand back toward the boy\'s and then snatch it.  See Youssif enjoy being a boy again »\\n\\nThe boy giggled inside a play area where sponge-like balls shot out of toy guns. It was a far different artillery than what he was used to seeing in central Baghdad, as recently as a week ago. He squealed with delight and raced around the room collecting as many balls as he could.\\n\\nHe rode a tram through the back stages at Universal Studios. At one point, the car shook. Fire and smoke filled the air, debris cascaded down and a big rig skidded toward the vehicle. The boy and his family survived the pretend earthquake unscathed.\\n\\n\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.\\n\\nThey also discussed that day nine months ago when masked men grabbed their son outside the family home, doused him in gas and set him on fire. His mother heard her boy screaming from inside.\\n\\nThe father sought help for his boy across Baghdad, but no one listened. He remembers his son\'s two months of hospitalization. The doctors didn\'t use anesthetics. He could hear his boy\'s piercing screams from the other side of the hospital.  Watch Youssif meet his doctor and play with his little sister »\\n\\nThe father knew that speaking to CNN would put his family\'s lives in jeopardy. The possibility of being killed was better than seeing his son suffer, he said.\\n\\n\\"Anything for Youssif,\\" he said. \\"We had to do it.\\"\\n\\nThey described a life of utter chaos in Baghdad. Neighbors had recently given birth to a baby girl. Shortly afterward, the father was kidnapped and killed. Then, there was the time when some girls wore tanktops and jeans. They were snatched off the street by gunmen.\\n\\nThe stories can be even more gruesome. The couple said they had heard reports that a young girl was kidnapped and beheaded --and her killers sewed a dog\'s head on the corpse and delivered it to her family\'s doorstep.\\n\\n\\"These are just some of the stories,\\" said Youssif\'s mother, Zainab.\\n\\nUnder Saddam Hussein, there was more security and stability, they said. There was running water and electricity most of the time. But still life was tough under the dictator, like the time when Zainab\'s uncle disappeared and was never heard from again after he read a \\"religious book,\\" she said.\\n\\nSitting in the parking lot of a Target in suburban Los Angeles, Youssif\'s father watched as husbands and wives, boyfriends and girlfriends, parents and their children, came and went. Some held hands. Others smiled and laughed.\\n\\n\\"Iraq finished,\\" he said in what few English words he knows.\\n\\nHe elaborated in Arabic: His homeland won\'t be enjoying such freedoms anytime soon. It\'s just not possible. Too much violence. Too many killings.\\n\\nHis two children have only seen war. But this week, the family has seen a much different side of America -- an outpouring of generosity and a peaceful nation at home. \\"It\'s been a dream,\\" the father said.\\n\\nHe used to do a lot of volunteer work back in Baghdad. \\"Maybe that\'s why I\'m being helped now,\\" the father said.\\n\\nAt Universal Studios, he looked out across the valley below. The sun glistened off treetops and buildings. It was a picturesque sight fit for a Hollywood movie.\\n\\n\\"Good America, good America,\\" he said in English. E-mail to a friend\\n\\nCNN\'s Arwa Damon contributed to this report.","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":4295,"question":"What did the boy say about Spider Man?","answer_char_ranges":"1017:1045,1065:1092,1124:1163|1124:1163|1124:1163","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"All right Youssif!\\" Spider-Man said after the boy mimicked his wrist movement.\\n\\nOther superheroes crowded around to get a closer look. Even the Green Goblin stopped his villainous ways to tell the boy hi. Youssif remained unfazed. He didn\'t take a liking to Spider-Man\'s nemesis.\\n\\nSpidey was just too cool.\\n\\n\\"It was my favorite thing,\\" the boy said later. \\"I want to see him again.\\"\\n\\nHe then felt compelled to add: \\"I know it\'s not the real Spider-Man.\\"","pred_ans":"i want to see him again","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":8742,"question":"apart from his wedding day, what did this day mean to dad?","answer_char_ranges":"2424:2433,2437:2450|2424:2433,2437:2450","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"happiest day of my life","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":10159,"question":"What was Youssif\'s favorite thing?","answer_char_ranges":"209:220|209:220,225:237,241:245,254:262|209:220,225:237,241:245,254:262","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"spider - man","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":24808,"question":"What was the boys name?","answer_char_ranges":"33:42|33:42","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"youssif","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":27671,"question":"What was the Dad\'s happiest day besides this day?","answer_char_ranges":"2399:2407|2399:2407","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"my wedding day","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":27784,"question":"what was the boy\'s favourite thing?","answer_char_ranges":"225:233,272:283|209:220|209:220","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"All right Youssif!\\" Spider-Man said after the boy mimicked his wrist movement.\\n\\nOther superheroes crowded around to get a closer look. Even the Green Goblin stopped his villainous ways to tell the boy hi. Youssif remained unfazed. He didn\'t take a liking to Spider-Man\'s nemesis.\\n\\nSpidey was just too cool.\\n\\n\\"It was my favorite thing,\\" the boy said later. \\"I want to see him again.\\"\\n\\nHe then felt compelled to add: \\"I know it\'s not the real Spider-Man.\\"","pred_ans":"i want to see him again","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":32328,"question":"What character was his favorite?","answer_char_ranges":"209:220|209:220","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"spider - man","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":36013,"question":"Who did Youssif meet?","answer_char_ranges":"209:220|1263:1322,209:220,853:866|149:177,190:202,204:237|209:220","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"209:220\\": 2, \\"1263:1322\\": 1}","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"his favorite superhero . youssif has always been a huge spider - man","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":37015,"question":"Who did the boy meet besides Spider-Man?","answer_char_ranges":"853:866|853:866","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"The father sought help for his boy across Baghdad, but no one listened. He remembers his son\'s two months of hospitalization. The doctors didn\'t use anesthetics. He could hear his boy\'s piercing screams from the other side of the hospital.  Watch Youssif meet his doctor and play with his little sister »\\n\\nThe father knew that speaking to CNN would put his family\'s lives in jeopardy. The possibility of being killed was better than seeing his son suffer, he said.","pred_ans":"his doctor and play with his little sister","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":48594,"question":"Was the dad happy?","answer_char_ranges":"None|2424:2450","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"2424:2450\\": 2}","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"this is the happiest day of my life","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":48636,"question":"who said \\"other than my wedding day,this is the happiest day of my life\\".","answer_char_ranges":"2347:2364|2347:2364","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"youssif \' s father","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":48647,"question":"Was it a happy day for dad","answer_char_ranges":"None|2384:2407,2412:2433,2437:2450","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"2412:2433\\": 2, \\"none\\": 1}","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"this is the happiest day of my life","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":50019,"question":"who did youssif also meet in universal studios?","answer_char_ranges":"272:283|209:262|1263:1281,1287:1308,1314:1322,272:283|272:287","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"1263:1281\\": 2}","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"spider - man","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":52452,"question":"Where did Youssif meet Lassie?","answer_char_ranges":"107:115,97:107|1870:1889|107:115,97:107","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"universal studios","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":55653,"question":"Who did youssif meet at universal","answer_char_ranges":"209:220|272:283|153:177,209:220|153:177,209:220","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"153:177\\": 1, \\"209:220\\": 2}","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"his favorite superhero . youssif has always been a huge spider - man","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":65432,"question":"What was the dad\'s happiest day?","answer_char_ranges":"2399:2407|2396:2407|2412:2424,2437:2450|None","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"2396:2407\\": 1, \\"2399:2407\\": 2}","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"my wedding day","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":72222,"question":"What did boy say to spider man","answer_char_ranges":"1017:1045|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1017:1045\\": 2}","para_text":"\\"All right Youssif!\\" Spider-Man said after the boy mimicked his wrist movement.\\n\\nOther superheroes crowded around to get a closer look. Even the Green Goblin stopped his villainous ways to tell the boy hi. Youssif remained unfazed. He didn\'t take a liking to Spider-Man\'s nemesis.\\n\\nSpidey was just too cool.\\n\\n\\"It was my favorite thing,\\" the boy said later. \\"I want to see him again.\\"\\n\\nHe then felt compelled to add: \\"I know it\'s not the real Spider-Man.\\"","pred_ans":"i want to see him again . \\"","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":77221,"question":"What did the boy say about Spider-Man?","answer_char_ranges":"1065:1092|1017:1045,1065:1092,1124:1150|1017:1045,1065:1092,1124:1163,225:241,2384:2420,241:245,2420:2450,245:262|1017:1045,1065:1092","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1065:1092\\": 1, \\"2420:2450\\": 1, \\"1124:1163\\": 1}","para_text":"\\"All right Youssif!\\" Spider-Man said after the boy mimicked his wrist movement.\\n\\nOther superheroes crowded around to get a closer look. Even the Green Goblin stopped his villainous ways to tell the boy hi. Youssif remained unfazed. He didn\'t take a liking to Spider-Man\'s nemesis.\\n\\nSpidey was just too cool.\\n\\n\\"It was my favorite thing,\\" the boy said later. \\"I want to see him again.\\"\\n\\nHe then felt compelled to add: \\"I know it\'s not the real Spider-Man.\\"","pred_ans":"i want to see him again","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":80877,"question":"Who did Youssif met at Universal Studios?","answer_char_ranges":"209:220|209:220","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"his favorite superhero . youssif has always been a huge spider - man","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":82654,"question":"What was the boy\'s favorite thing?","answer_char_ranges":"166:177,225:237|225:233,272:283|225:237|209:220","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"225:237\\": 1, \\"none\\": 1, \\"209:220\\": 1}","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"spider - man","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":86039,"question":"Where did Youssif meet spongebob,Lassie and an orangutan.","answer_char_ranges":"107:115,97:107|107:115,94:107|107:115,97:107","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"universal studios","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":87536,"question":"What was the boy\'s name?","answer_char_ranges":"33:42|33:42","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"All right Youssif!\\" Spider-Man said after the boy mimicked his wrist movement.\\n\\nOther superheroes crowded around to get a closer look. Even the Green Goblin stopped his villainous ways to tell the boy hi. Youssif remained unfazed. He didn\'t take a liking to Spider-Man\'s nemesis.\\n\\nSpidey was just too cool.\\n\\n\\"It was my favorite thing,\\" the boy said later. \\"I want to see him again.\\"\\n\\nHe then felt compelled to add: \\"I know it\'s not the real Spider-Man.\\"","pred_ans":"youssif","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":91374,"question":"Where did the meetings take place?","answer_char_ranges":"None|107:115,87:107","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2, \\"87:107\\": 1}","para_text":"\\"All right Youssif!\\" Spider-Man said after the boy mimicked his wrist movement.\\n\\nOther superheroes crowded around to get a closer look. Even the Green Goblin stopped his villainous ways to tell the boy hi. Youssif remained unfazed. He didn\'t take a liking to Spider-Man\'s nemesis.\\n\\nSpidey was just too cool.\\n\\n\\"It was my favorite thing,\\" the boy said later. \\"I want to see him again.\\"\\n\\nHe then felt compelled to add: \\"I know it\'s not the real Spider-Man.\\"","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":95222,"question":"When was dad also this happy?","answer_char_ranges":"2399:2412|2399:2412","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"my wedding day","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":96787,"question":"what did the boy say was his favorite thing","answer_char_ranges":"209:220,225:237|225:237,272:283|209:220,225:237","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":99571,"question":"What made this the happiest day of his life?","answer_char_ranges":"None|209:220","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"209:220\\": 2}","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"my wedding day","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":101785,"question":"what is boys favorite thing?","answer_char_ranges":"209:237|209:220|209:220","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"spider - man","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":104386,"question":"what did dad say?","answer_char_ranges":"2079:2100|2079:2100","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"this is the happiest day of my life","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":106038,"question":"What did the dad say?","answer_char_ranges":"2079:2100,2279:2347,2384:2450,3226:3236,3240:3250,4360:4377,4447:4568,4736:4757,4830:4871,5051:5081|2079:2100|2079:2100,2279:2347,3226:3250,3259:3278,4360:4377,4736:4757,4830:4871|2079:2100","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"4830:4871\\": 1, \\"2079:2100\\": 2}","para_text":"\\"Even I was scared,\\" the dad said.\\n\\n\\"Well, I wasn\'t,\\" Youssif replied.\\n\\nThe father and mother grinned from ear to ear throughout the day. Youssif pushed his 14-month-old sister, Ayaa, in a stroller.\\n\\n\\"Did you even need to ask us if we were interested in coming here?\\" Youssif\'s father said in amazement.\\n\\n\\"Other than my wedding day, this is the happiest day of my life,\\" he said.\\n\\nJust a day earlier, the mother and father talked about their journey out of Iraq and to the United States.","pred_ans":"\\" even i was scared","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":106143,"question":"who is youssif?","answer_char_ranges":"42:75|46:75|46:75","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LOS ANGELES, California (CNN) -- Youssif, the 5-year-old burned Iraqi boy, rounded the corner at Universal Studios when suddenly the little boy hero met his favorite superhero.\\n\\nYoussif has always been a huge Spider-Man fan. Meeting him was \\"my favorite thing,\\" he said.\\n\\nSpider-Man was right smack dab in front of him, riding a four-wheeler amid a convoy of other superheroes. The legendary climber of buildings and fighter of evil dismounted, walked over to Youssif and introduced himself.","pred_ans":"burned iraqi boy","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/44fc3a2bc441a674f1ebdeabae73278977909db4.story","story_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.\\n\\nIslamic extremists in Algeria and other North African countries have struck several times in recent years.\\n\\nAn al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":4663,"question":"trash4564216464","answer_char_ranges":"None|None","is_answer_absent":1,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"trash4564216464 [SEP]","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":11320,"question":"What was destroyed in the blast?","answer_char_ranges":"167:177,180:188|372:389|372:389","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"about 20 houses","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":14407,"question":"WHo said they were responsibble for the blase","answer_char_ranges":"822:831|822:831","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"the algerian press service","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":21988,"question":"what time I happened Thenia attack?","answer_char_ranges":"200:217|209:217|None|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"209:217\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"tuesday","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":22415,"question":"where was the bombing of Al Qaeda that killed 4?","answer_char_ranges":"30:38|953:962|953:962","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"naciria","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":25493,"question":"Where is the attact occur?","answer_char_ranges":"30:38|30:38","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"thenia","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":27594,"question":"What city did the attack occur in?","answer_char_ranges":"180:188|180:188,271:279|180:188","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"thenia","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":27911,"question":"Where did the attack occur?","answer_char_ranges":"200:209,217:279|30:38|217:334|263:291,302:334","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"217:334\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"thenia","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":33059,"question":"Who took responsability for the bombing?","answer_char_ranges":"None|None","is_answer_absent":1,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"al qaeda","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":36030,"question":"In what cityy did the attack happen","answer_char_ranges":"180:188|200:209,263:279|271:279|271:279","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"263:279\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"thenia","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":41799,"question":"which group took responsibility for the bombing?","answer_char_ranges":"822:831|822:831","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"al qaeda","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":43599,"question":"354d6+84684gf6ser4g864sr6g8rg","answer_char_ranges":"None|None","is_answer_absent":1,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"[SEP]","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":47048,"question":"Who took responsibility for the bombing?","answer_char_ranges":"587:606|587:606","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"al qaeda","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":57494,"question":"Who took responsibility?","answer_char_ranges":"584:606|587:614,822:836|587:614|584:606","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"584:606\\": 2}","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"al qaeda","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":62207,"question":"Who took responsibility for the attack?","answer_char_ranges":"822:831|822:831","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"al qaeda","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":68712,"question":"Where did the attacks occur?","answer_char_ranges":"225:279|30:38|271:279,30:38|271:279,314:334","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"225:279\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"thenia","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":72205,"question":"What was the amount of victims of the attack?","answer_char_ranges":"42:78|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"42:78\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"three","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":75527,"question":"The blast did what?","answer_char_ranges":"362:389|42:78|42:55,66:78|362:389","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"42:78\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"destroyed about 20 houses","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":77727,"question":"where did the attack occur in Thenia?","answer_char_ranges":"217:256|217:256","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"near an office housing judicial police","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":79567,"question":"what is the count of houses destroyed and people injured?","answer_char_ranges":"378:381,49:55|378:381,66:78|378:381,66:78","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"20","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":82914,"question":"trash3584648386468","answer_char_ranges":"None|None","is_answer_absent":1,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"trash3584648386468 [SEP]","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":84029,"question":"What did the blast destroy?","answer_char_ranges":"378:389|372:389|378:389","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"about 20 houses","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":90536,"question":"there was some died in the explosion?","answer_char_ranges":"42:62|42:62","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"three","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":99295,"question":"Where is the office?","answer_char_ranges":"285:291,302:334|256:334|263:291,302:334|271:279","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"256:334\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"thenia","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":99853,"question":"Who took responsibility for the January bombing?","answer_char_ranges":"822:836,860:862,870:872|476:495|822:831,870:872|822:831","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"822:831\\": 2}","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"al qaeda","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":109110,"question":"what kind of damage was done","answer_char_ranges":"352:389|362:389,42:62,66:78|362:389|362:389,42:78","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"362:389\\": 1, \\"352:389\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"the blast destroyed about 20 houses","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":116405,"question":"the blast destroy how many house?","answer_char_ranges":"352:356,362:389|372:389|378:389|378:389","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"362:389\\": 2, \\"378:389\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\\n\\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\\n\\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\\n\\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.","pred_ans":"20","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":116601,"question":"Who took responsibility for the bombing that killed four?","answer_char_ranges":"587:606|822:836,860:872|584:606|822:831","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"822:831\\": 2}","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"al qaeda","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":119217,"question":"When did the bombing that killed four take place?","answer_char_ranges":"30:38|862:870|209:217|189:217","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"862:870\\": 2, \\"189:217\\": 1}","para_text":"An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister\'s headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\\n\\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"january 2","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/30cb674030b01014d2c87b92f09152857e249631.story","story_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.\\n\\nA statement from Nigerian Breweries on Monday said Ogadje died suddenly and he was thought to have drowned.\\n\\n\\"All attempts to revive him by the attendant medical team and the lifeguards, including his fellow contestants, failed,\\" said Nigerian Breweries, which is majority-owned by the Dutch giant. Broadcasting had been due to start on Thursday.\\n\\nIn the show, the weakest contestants are evicted one by one until a winner emerges. The prize money is a big attraction in a country where most people live in extreme poverty and benefit little from Nigeria\'s oil wealth.\\n\\nThe winner was to get 5 million naira (about $39,000) in cash, a four-wheel drive jeep and another 500,000 naira (about $3,900) to buy clothes. The winner could also have expected to become an instant celebrity, attracting sponsorship deals.\\n\\nThe Ultimate Search, which started in 2004, gets high ratings. E-mail to a friend","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":1415,"question":"What age was Mr Ogadje","answer_char_ranges":"212:220,228:232|228:232|228:232","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"25","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":12141,"question":"WHAT WAS HE PREPARING FOR?","answer_char_ranges":"340:366|112:124,128:141|49:63|128:141,340:366","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"128:141\\": 1, \\"340:366\\": 2}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"gulder ultimate search , \\"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":20434,"question":"What was Anthony Odagje doing at the time of his death?","answer_char_ranges":"528:537|259:366|112:141|528:537","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"259:366\\": 2}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"gone to shere hills lake","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":25865,"question":"WHERE DID ANTHONY OGADJE REPORTEDLY DROWN?","answer_char_ranges":"271:321|271:321","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"shere hills lake","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":27466,"question":"Who sponsors the program","answer_char_ranges":"159:170|146:181|146:181","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"heineken \' s local unit which is sponsoring the show","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":28569,"question":"Which Dutch brewer sponsored the program","answer_char_ranges":"159:181|159:181,187:211|159:170|159:170","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"159:181\\": 2}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"heineken","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":40714,"question":"who is anthony?","answer_char_ranges":"247:259,332:336,340:366|220:232|247:259|247:259","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2, \\"220:232\\": 1}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":43142,"question":"where did anthony drowned?","answer_char_ranges":"271:288|271:321|271:321","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"shere hills lake","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":54527,"question":"What age was Anthony Ogadje?","answer_char_ranges":"228:232|228:232","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"25","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":61622,"question":"Who drowned in Shere HIlls Lake?","answer_char_ranges":"480:487|212:228|212:228","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"anthony ogadje","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":63321,"question":"Who sponsors the show \\"Gulder Ultimate Search\\"?","answer_char_ranges":"146:181|146:170|159:170|146:170","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"159:170\\": 2}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"heineken","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":67616,"question":"What age was Anthony Ogadje when he died?","answer_char_ranges":"228:232|228:232","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"25","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":72601,"question":"Which country is Heineken from?","answer_char_ranges":"146:152|146:152","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"dutch","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":74917,"question":"What program does Heineken sponsor?","answer_char_ranges":"340:366|28:63|340:366","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"nigeria \' s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program , said dutch brewer heineken \' s local unit which is sponsoring the show . anthony ogadje , 25 , and nine other contestants had gone to shere hills lake in nigeria \' s hilly plateau state to prepare for the \\" gulder ultimate search","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":76899,"question":"What show was he preparing for?","answer_char_ranges":"340:366|340:366","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"gulder ultimate search","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":77472,"question":"Where did Anthony Ogadje die?","answer_char_ranges":"271:321|271:288|271:301|271:321","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"271:288\\": 1, \\"271:321\\": 1, \\"271:301\\": 1}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"shere hills lake","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":77684,"question":"Who were the sponsors of his show?","answer_char_ranges":"159:170|146:181,446:465|159:170","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"dutch brewer heineken","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":83097,"question":"Which company sponsors the show Gulder Ultimate Search?","answer_char_ranges":"159:170|146:170|146:181,187:205|159:170","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"159:170\\": 2, \\"146:170\\": 1}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"heineken","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":86236,"question":"Where did Anthony Ogadje drown","answer_char_ranges":"271:288|271:288","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"shere hills lake","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":96287,"question":"What happened?","answer_char_ranges":"101:141,28:101|101:141,28:101","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"a contestant drowned","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":97529,"question":"What was he doing?","answer_char_ranges":"324:366|101:141|321:366|112:124,132:141","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"101:141\\": 2}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"gone to shere hills lake in nigeria \' s hilly plateau state to prepare for the \\" gulder ultimate search , \\"","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":99568,"question":"WHAT COMPANY SPONSORS THE PROGRAM?","answer_char_ranges":"159:170|146:170|146:181|146:181","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"146:170\\": 2, \\"146:181\\": 1}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"heineken","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":101772,"question":"who was the sponsor?","answer_char_ranges":"446:465|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"446:465\\": 2}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"heineken","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":107441,"question":"What was his age?","answer_char_ranges":"228:232|228:232","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"25","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":113106,"question":"what is heineken?","answer_char_ranges":"146:159|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"146:159\\": 2, \\"none\\": 1}","para_text":"LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria\'s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken\'s local unit which is sponsoring the show.\\n\\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria\'s hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \\"Gulder Ultimate Search,\\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.","pred_ans":"dutch brewer","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/d5342fb6d8d522f336f2ce34eaa6e62446c0da2e.story","story_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.\\n\\nDressed in a tailored, black pantsuit, Lafave said she had \\"innocent\\" physical contact with a female co-worker she knew as under age 18.  Watch Lafave in the courtroom »\\n\\nAt the time, she and the 17-year-old hostess worked at Danny Boy\'s, a small restaurant in the Tampa, Florida, area.\\n\\nLafave, 27, pleaded guilty in November 2005 to having sex with a 14-year-old boy and was sentenced to three years under house arrest and seven years of probation.\\n\\nLafave was required to register as a sex offender and ordered not to have any contact with minors. A tracking device she carries as part of her probation went off in court, prompting the prosecutor to observe, \\"I think she\'s accounted for.\\"\\n\\nLafave acknowledged she was aware that hugs and other forms of physical contact -- as well as conversations about sex -- with minors violated terms of her probation. She referred to the sexually explicit conversations at work as just \\"girl talk.\\"\\n\\nLafave denied talking about her sex life with co-workers. \\"I don\'t speak that way about my personal life,\\" she said. But she added that her co-workers spoke freely about sex in a \\"small group setting.\\"\\n\\nWhile other co-workers socialized outside work, Lafave said, the 17-year-old was not included in those outings.\\n\\nAsked why she hugged the young co-worker, Lafave explained it was a small restaurant with a casual atmosphere where co-workers felt like family. The contact came, she said, \\"out of my good nature, that\'s the way it worked.\\"\\n\\nThe contacts that led to Thursday\'s probation violation hearing first surfaced during two polygraph tests administered as part of Lafave\'s court-ordered supervision.\\n\\nShe received a verbal reprimand a year ago, according to testimony. When the behavior continued, her probation officer asked a judge to find her in violation.\\n\\nShe was ordered to quit the restaurant job and now works as a receptionist in her mother\'s beauty shop.\\n\\nIn the past, Lafave has said she suffers from bipolar disorder and is receiving treatment. E-mail to a friend","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":4486,"question":"What are the terms of her probation","answer_char_ranges":"919:995|1177:1218,1221:1256,1259:1280,1286:1289,919:946,950:995|254:304|907:995","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"907:995\\": 1, \\"919:995\\": 1, \\"254:304\\": 1}","para_text":"Lafave acknowledged she was aware that hugs and other forms of physical contact -- as well as conversations about sex -- with minors violated terms of her probation. She referred to the sexually explicit conversations at work as just \\"girl talk.\\"\\n\\nLafave denied talking about her sex life with co-workers. \\"I don\'t speak that way about my personal life,\\" she said. But she added that her co-workers spoke freely about sex in a \\"small group setting.\\"","pred_ans":"lafave acknowledged she was aware that hugs and other forms of physical contact - - as well as conversations about sex - - with minors violated terms of her probation","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":5884,"question":"What did the judge say to Lafave?","answer_char_ranges":"373:404,405:431|405:431|405:431","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"the violation was \\" not willful and substantial . \\"","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":8384,"question":"What minimum age is Lafave prohibited from having contact with?","answer_char_ranges":"None|247:251,254:274,287:304","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"287:304\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"18","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":10621,"question":"What does a judge warn Debra lafave?","answer_char_ranges":"None|413:431","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"413:431\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":15522,"question":"What warning did the judge give Debra Lafave?","answer_char_ranges":"None|2094:2138,2162:2221,2227:2253,405:443","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2, \\"405:443\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":17337,"question":"What did judge find?","answer_char_ranges":"104:157,15:23,27:64,9:15|348:404|104:127,15:23,9:15|104:157","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"104:127\\": 1, \\"none\\": 1, \\"104:157\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"debra lafave , the former florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student , violated her probation by hugging a young co - worker , a florida judge found thursday","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":29280,"question":"What does the probation forbid her from?","answer_char_ranges":"130:157|274:304|1177:1182,1192:1198,1201:1218,1232:1256,1259:1271,130:138,140:157,254:266,274:282,287:304,958:962,965:995|896:907,950:970,974:995","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"965:995\\": 1, \\"274:304\\": 2}","para_text":"At the time, she and the 17-year-old hostess worked at Danny Boy\'s, a small restaurant in the Tampa, Florida, area.\\n\\nLafave, 27, pleaded guilty in November 2005 to having sex with a 14-year-old boy and was sentenced to three years under house arrest and seven years of probation.","pred_ans":"having sex","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":34247,"question":"What does Debra Lafave\'s probation forbid her from doing?","answer_char_ranges":"266:304|266:304","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"have contact with anyone under 18","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":39604,"question":"What does Lafave probation forbid?","answer_char_ranges":"269:304|903:907,950:970,974:995|130:157|247:304","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"269:304\\": 2, \\"247:304\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"she is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":41229,"question":"what did she do?","answer_char_ranges":"104:157|104:157,15:23,9:15|499:545|77:104","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"104:157\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"violated her probation by hugging a young co - worker","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":49112,"question":"what else did the judge say?","answer_char_ranges":"405:431|405:431","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"the violation was \\" not willful and substantial . \\"","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":50273,"question":"Who was found to be in violation of probation?","answer_char_ranges":"15:23,9:15|104:117,15:23,9:15|15:23,9:15","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"debra lafave","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":52214,"question":"What were the charges against the former teacher?","answer_char_ranges":"834:895|104:157|104:157","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"having sex with a student","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":59627,"question":"what forbids Lafave\'s probation to Debra?","answer_char_ranges":"958:962,965:970,974:995|None","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"974:995\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"she is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":59701,"question":"What did the judge find the former teacher for?","answer_char_ranges":"77:104|104:157|None|104:157","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"bad_question\\": 1, \\"104:157\\": 1, \\"77:104\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"having sex with a student","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":64710,"question":"Who is she not allowed to be in contact with?","answer_char_ranges":"287:304|1264:1271|965:974,987:995|287:304","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"1264:1271\\": 2, \\"287:304\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"anyone under 18","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":68543,"question":"What was Lafave\'s former job?","answer_char_ranges":"None|42:64","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"42:64\\": 2}","para_text":"She was ordered to quit the restaurant job and now works as a receptionist in her mother\'s beauty shop.\\n\\nIn the past, Lafave has said she suffers from bipolar disorder and is receiving treatment. E-mail to a friend","pred_ans":"restaurant","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":70350,"question":"What are the terms of Lafave\'s probation?","answer_char_ranges":"907:995|254:304|247:304|1177:1182,1186:1218,1232:1256,1259:1271","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"247:304\\": 1, \\"907:995\\": 2}","para_text":"Lafave acknowledged she was aware that hugs and other forms of physical contact -- as well as conversations about sex -- with minors violated terms of her probation. She referred to the sexually explicit conversations at work as just \\"girl talk.\\"\\n\\nLafave denied talking about her sex life with co-workers. \\"I don\'t speak that way about my personal life,\\" she said. But she added that her co-workers spoke freely about sex in a \\"small group setting.\\"","pred_ans":"hugs and other forms of physical contact - - as well as conversations about sex - - with minors violated terms","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":72741,"question":"What did the judge find former teacher","answer_char_ranges":"323:348|104:157|104:127|104:127","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"104:157\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"debra lafave","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":72957,"question":"what judge warns Debra?","answer_char_ranges":"405:431|405:431","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"a florida","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":73662,"question":"What is Debra Lafave\'s occupation?","answer_char_ranges":"42:64|42:64","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"florida middle school teacher","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":81183,"question":"what is the teacher accused of?","answer_char_ranges":"222:247|74:104|None|77:104","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"74:104\\": 2, \\"77:104\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"having sex with a student","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":85898,"question":"Will Debra Lafave go to jail","answer_char_ranges":"319:332|309:332|319:332","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"the judge did not send lafave to jail","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":86184,"question":"What is the name of the teacher in the case?","answer_char_ranges":"15:23,9:15|15:23,9:15","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"debra lafave","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":87035,"question":"Does the judge find?","answer_char_ranges":"373:404|104:127|None|348:355,373:404","is_answer_absent":0.25,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"the judge did not send lafave to jail","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":92642,"question":"What does lafave\'s Probation forbid her from?","answer_char_ranges":"247:304|274:304|965:995|1192:1218,1259:1271","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"965:995\\": 1, \\"274:304\\": 2}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"have contact with anyone under 18","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":93922,"question":"what was violated?","answer_char_ranges":"117:127|113:127|113:138,140:157|113:127","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2, \\"117:127\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"probation","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":101849,"question":"Who was spared from jail?","answer_char_ranges":"15:23,9:15|332:339|15:23,9:15","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"debra lafave","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":102566,"question":"Did the judge find the teacher in violation of her probation?","answer_char_ranges":"104:113|104:113,157:167,173:179|104:113,15:23,1952:1963,1983:2093,2162:2171,2205:2221,2227:2230,305:313,323:359,369:404,9:15|323:359,369:404","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2, \\"173:179\\": 1}","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"violated her probation by hugging a young co - worker , a florida judge found thursday","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":115472,"question":"What was the former teacher\'s name?","answer_char_ranges":"15:23,9:15|15:23,9:15","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\\n\\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\\n\\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \\"not willful and substantial.\\"\\n\\n\\"Please don\'t come back,\\" he scolded.","pred_ans":"debra lafave","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]},{"story_id":"./cnn/stories/35ae4229bbd571d86bb817df03b3784dc8cbf660.story","story_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"\\n\\nGravell made his debut for Wales against France in 1975, three years after helping his club side Llanelli to their famous win over the touring All Blacks.\\n\\nIn all he made 23 appearances for what was then a dominant Wales side, winning Grand Slams in 1976 and 1978, and played all four Tests on the Lions\' tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nAfter retiring as a player in 1985, Gravell became president of Llanelli RFC and the Llanelli Scarlets. He also pursued a career as an actor and a respected rugby broadcaster.\\n\\nEarlier this year, Gravell had his right leg amputated below the knee following complications linked with his diabetes but he had been recovering well.\\n\\nWRU chief executive Roger Lewis said: \\"We are all in total shock because Ray was so full of life even through the difficult health problems he suffered recently.\\n\\n\\"He was a wonderful ambassador for rugby and for Wales and a great example of how the game can bring out the best in a man.\\n\\n\\"As a player, he always gave a huge amount of respect to his opponents but never gave an inch of ground to anyone he faced on the field of play.\\n\\n\\"It is a measure of the man that he forged rugby friendships which lasted long after his playing days up until the present day.\\" E-mail to a friend","questions":[{"Unnamed: 0":12557,"question":"What was his current occupation?","answer_char_ranges":"None|861:914,945:951,967:986","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"861:914\\": 1, \\"967:986\\": 1, \\"945:951\\": 1}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"center","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":19772,"question":"What was his age?","answer_char_ranges":"110:114|105:114|110:114","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"56","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":22410,"question":"what position did ray gravell play?","answer_char_ranges":"743:754|18:56|49:56|49:56","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"49:56\\": 1, \\"18:56\\": 2}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"center","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":22421,"question":"Where was he on holiday?","answer_char_ranges":"294:335|294:335","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"mallorca","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":25885,"question":"What did he do after retiring?","answer_char_ranges":"825:914|861:914|846:914,917:986|861:914,945:951,967:986","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"846:914\\": 1, \\"917:986\\": 2}","para_text":"In all he made 23 appearances for what was then a dominant Wales side, winning Grand Slams in 1976 and 1978, and played all four Tests on the Lions\' tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nAfter retiring as a player in 1985, Gravell became president of Llanelli RFC and the Llanelli Scarlets. He also pursued a career as an actor and a respected rugby broadcaster.\\n\\nEarlier this year, Gravell had his right leg amputated below the knee following complications linked with his diabetes but he had been recovering well.","pred_ans":"became president of llanelli rfc","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":29694,"question":"Where was he and his family holidaying","answer_char_ranges":"294:335|294:335","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"spanish mediterranean island of mallorca","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":32180,"question":"Who died aged 56?","answer_char_ranges":"56:68|56:68","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"ray gravell","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":36742,"question":"What else did Ray Gravell do?","answer_char_ranges":"917:986|1014:1042,166:188,192:242,640:664,669:733,72:77,733:739,743:784,77:80,784:809,80:92,854:914,922:930,92:98,930:986,98:105|861:871,874:887,895:914,945:951,967:986|945:951,967:986","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 1, \\"640:664\\": 1, \\"930:986\\": 1}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"played on the lions tour of south africa","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":42271,"question":"At what age has Ray Gravell died?","answer_char_ranges":"110:114|105:114|105:114,77:105|110:114","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"105:114\\": 1, \\"110:114\\": 2}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"56","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":44798,"question":"What age was Ray gravell","answer_char_ranges":"110:114|110:114","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"56","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":50186,"question":"What age was Ray Gravell when he died?","answer_char_ranges":"110:114|110:114","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"56","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":52828,"question":"What other careers did Ray Gravell pursue?","answer_char_ranges":"854:932,939:986|942:986|945:951,967:986|561:580,861:914,945:951,967:986","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"939:986\\": 1, \\"942:986\\": 1, \\"967:986\\": 1}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"wales and british lions center","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":56523,"question":"What age was Ray Gravell at his death?","answer_char_ranges":"105:114,56:77|110:114|110:114","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"56","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":58677,"question":"when did ray gravell die?","answer_char_ranges":"None|92:105","is_answer_absent":0.5,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"none\\": 2}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"56","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":58822,"question":"What was Ray Gravell\'s age at the time of his death.","answer_char_ranges":"105:114,68:77|110:114|110:114","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"56","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":62192,"question":"What did he work as after retiring?","answer_char_ranges":"861:914,945:951,967:986|846:914,917:930,932:939,945:955,967:986|861:914|854:914,917:986","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"861:914\\": 1, \\"854:914\\": 2}","para_text":"In all he made 23 appearances for what was then a dominant Wales side, winning Grand Slams in 1976 and 1978, and played all four Tests on the Lions\' tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nAfter retiring as a player in 1985, Gravell became president of Llanelli RFC and the Llanelli Scarlets. He also pursued a career as an actor and a respected rugby broadcaster.\\n\\nEarlier this year, Gravell had his right leg amputated below the knee following complications linked with his diabetes but he had been recovering well.","pred_ans":"actor and a respected rugby broadcaster","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":66261,"question":"what did gravell do after retiring?","answer_char_ranges":"854:986|854:887|854:914,945:951,957:986|854:986","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"854:887\\": 2}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"died","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":68816,"question":"who is ray gravell?","answer_char_ranges":"35:56|18:56|18:56","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"former wales and british lions center","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":82653,"question":"what did he work at after retiring?","answer_char_ranges":"854:914|861:914|861:887|861:914,945:951,967:986","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"861:887\\": 2}","para_text":"In all he made 23 appearances for what was then a dominant Wales side, winning Grand Slams in 1976 and 1978, and played all four Tests on the Lions\' tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nAfter retiring as a player in 1985, Gravell became president of Llanelli RFC and the Llanelli Scarlets. He also pursued a career as an actor and a respected rugby broadcaster.\\n\\nEarlier this year, Gravell had his right leg amputated below the knee following complications linked with his diabetes but he had been recovering well.","pred_ans":"president of llanelli rfc and the llanelli scarlets . he also pursued a career as an actor and a respected rugby broadcaster","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":83036,"question":"Which international teams did Ray Gravell play for?","answer_char_ranges":"25:49|182:188|206:233|25:49","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"25:49\\": 2, \\"182:188\\": 1}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"wales and british lions","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":90572,"question":"where was he on holiday with his family?","answer_char_ranges":"326:335|287:323|294:323,326:335|287:335","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"294:323\\": 1, \\"287:335\\": 2}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"mallorca","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":103398,"question":"What type of work did he do after retirement.","answer_char_ranges":"846:914,917:986|846:914,917:986","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":105033,"question":"What did he do after retirement","answer_char_ranges":"861:914,945:951,957:986|854:871,874:887,891:914,945:951,967:986|846:914|854:914","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"861:914\\": 1, \\"846:914\\": 2}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"on holiday","exact_match":0,"class":0,"is_correct_para":0},{"Unnamed: 0":107082,"question":"Where was he on holidays","answer_char_ranges":"326:335|326:335","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"spanish mediterranean island of mallorca","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":118026,"question":"Where was he in holiday?","answer_char_ranges":"290:335|326:335|326:335","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"mallorca","exact_match":1,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1},{"Unnamed: 0":118971,"question":"Where was Ray Gravell when he died?","answer_char_ranges":"260:271,287:335|251:348|326:335|326:335","is_answer_absent":0,"is_question_bad":"?","validated_answers":"{\\"251:348\\": 1, \\"287:335\\": 2}","para_text":"CARDIFF, Wales -- Former Wales and British Lions center Ray Gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56, the Welsh Rugby Union (WRU) has announced.\\n\\nGravell won 23 caps for Wales and played on the Lions tour of South Africa in 1980.\\n\\nGravell had been on holiday with his family in the Spanish Mediterranean island of Mallorca at the time.\\n\\nA WRU statement praised Gravell as being \\"a man who epitomized the passion, flair and dignity of his beloved Welsh nation.\\"","pred_ans":"cardiff , wales - - former wales and british lions center ray gravell has died of a suspected heart attack aged 56 , the welsh rugby union ( wru ) has announced . gravell won 23 caps for wales and played on the lions tour of south africa in 1980 . gravell had been on holiday with his family in the spanish mediterranean island of mallorca","exact_match":0,"class":1,"is_correct_para":1}]}]')},402:function(e,t,n){"use strict";var r=n(318);n.n(r).a},403:function(e,t,n){(t=n(5)(!1)).push([e.i,".font-size-6{font-size:.375rem!important}.font-size-8{font-size:.5rem!important}.font-size-10{font-size:.625rem!important}.font-size-12{font-size:.75rem!important}.font-size-14{font-size:.875rem!important}.font-size-16{font-size:1rem!important}.font-size-18{font-size:1.125rem!important}.font-size-20{font-size:1.25rem!important}.font-size-22{font-size:1.375rem!important}.font-size-24{font-size:1.5rem!important}.font-size-26{font-size:1.625rem!important}.font-size-28{font-size:1.75rem!important}.font-size-30{font-size:1.875rem!important}.font-size-32{font-size:2rem!important}.font-size-34{font-size:2.125rem!important}.font-size-36{font-size:2.25rem!important}.font-size-38{font-size:2.375rem!important}.font-size-40{font-size:2.5rem!important}.font-size-42{font-size:2.625rem!important}.font-size-44{font-size:2.75rem!important}.font-size-46{font-size:2.875rem!important}.font-size-48{font-size:3rem!important}.font-size-50{font-size:3.125rem!important}.font-size-52{font-size:3.25rem!important}.font-size-54{font-size:3.375rem!important}.font-size-56{font-size:3.5rem!important}.font-size-58{font-size:3.625rem!important}.font-size-60{font-size:3.75rem!important}@media(max-width:559px){.font-size-sm-6{font-size:.375rem!important}.font-size-sm-8{font-size:.5rem!important}.font-size-sm-10{font-size:.625rem!important}.font-size-sm-12{font-size:.75rem!important}.font-size-sm-14{font-size:.875rem!important}.font-size-sm-16{font-size:1rem!important}.font-size-sm-18{font-size:1.125rem!important}.font-size-sm-20{font-size:1.25rem!important}.font-size-sm-22{font-size:1.375rem!important}.font-size-sm-24{font-size:1.5rem!important}.font-size-sm-26{font-size:1.625rem!important}.font-size-sm-28{font-size:1.75rem!important}.font-size-sm-30{font-size:1.875rem!important}.font-size-sm-32{font-size:2rem!important}.font-size-sm-34{font-size:2.125rem!important}.font-size-sm-36{font-size:2.25rem!important}.font-size-sm-38{font-size:2.375rem!important}.font-size-sm-40{font-size:2.5rem!important}.font-size-sm-42{font-size:2.625rem!important}.font-size-sm-44{font-size:2.75rem!important}.font-size-sm-46{font-size:2.875rem!important}.font-size-sm-48{font-size:3rem!important}.font-size-sm-50{font-size:3.125rem!important}.font-size-sm-52{font-size:3.25rem!important}.font-size-sm-54{font-size:3.375rem!important}.font-size-sm-56{font-size:3.5rem!important}.font-size-sm-58{font-size:3.625rem!important}.font-size-sm-60{font-size:3.75rem!important}}@media(min-width:960px){.font-size-md-6{font-size:.375rem!important}.font-size-md-8{font-size:.5rem!important}.font-size-md-10{font-size:.625rem!important}.font-size-md-12{font-size:.75rem!important}.font-size-md-14{font-size:.875rem!important}.font-size-md-16{font-size:1rem!important}.font-size-md-18{font-size:1.125rem!important}.font-size-md-20{font-size:1.25rem!important}.font-size-md-22{font-size:1.375rem!important}.font-size-md-24{font-size:1.5rem!important}.font-size-md-26{font-size:1.625rem!important}.font-size-md-28{font-size:1.75rem!important}.font-size-md-30{font-size:1.875rem!important}.font-size-md-32{font-size:2rem!important}.font-size-md-34{font-size:2.125rem!important}.font-size-md-36{font-size:2.25rem!important}.font-size-md-38{font-size:2.375rem!important}.font-size-md-40{font-size:2.5rem!important}.font-size-md-42{font-size:2.625rem!important}.font-size-md-44{font-size:2.75rem!important}.font-size-md-46{font-size:2.875rem!important}.font-size-md-48{font-size:3rem!important}.font-size-md-50{font-size:3.125rem!important}.font-size-md-52{font-size:3.25rem!important}.font-size-md-54{font-size:3.375rem!important}.font-size-md-56{font-size:3.5rem!important}.font-size-md-58{font-size:3.625rem!important}.font-size-md-60{font-size:3.75rem!important}}@media(min-width:1264px){.font-size-lg-6{font-size:.375rem!important}.font-size-lg-8{font-size:.5rem!important}.font-size-lg-10{font-size:.625rem!important}.font-size-lg-12{font-size:.75rem!important}.font-size-lg-14{font-size:.875rem!important}.font-size-lg-16{font-size:1rem!important}.font-size-lg-18{font-size:1.125rem!important}.font-size-lg-20{font-size:1.25rem!important}.font-size-lg-22{font-size:1.375rem!important}.font-size-lg-24{font-size:1.5rem!important}.font-size-lg-26{font-size:1.625rem!important}.font-size-lg-28{font-size:1.75rem!important}.font-size-lg-30{font-size:1.875rem!important}.font-size-lg-32{font-size:2rem!important}.font-size-lg-34{font-size:2.125rem!important}.font-size-lg-36{font-size:2.25rem!important}.font-size-lg-38{font-size:2.375rem!important}.font-size-lg-40{font-size:2.5rem!important}.font-size-lg-42{font-size:2.625rem!important}.font-size-lg-44{font-size:2.75rem!important}.font-size-lg-46{font-size:2.875rem!important}.font-size-lg-48{font-size:3rem!important}.font-size-lg-50{font-size:3.125rem!important}.font-size-lg-52{font-size:3.25rem!important}.font-size-lg-54{font-size:3.375rem!important}.font-size-lg-56{font-size:3.5rem!important}.font-size-lg-58{font-size:3.625rem!important}.font-size-lg-60{font-size:3.75rem!important}}@media(min-width:1904px){.font-size-xl-6{font-size:.375rem!important}.font-size-xl-8{font-size:.5rem!important}.font-size-xl-10{font-size:.625rem!important}.font-size-xl-12{font-size:.75rem!important}.font-size-xl-14{font-size:.875rem!important}.font-size-xl-16{font-size:1rem!important}.font-size-xl-18{font-size:1.125rem!important}.font-size-xl-20{font-size:1.25rem!important}.font-size-xl-22{font-size:1.375rem!important}.font-size-xl-24{font-size:1.5rem!important}.font-size-xl-26{font-size:1.625rem!important}.font-size-xl-28{font-size:1.75rem!important}.font-size-xl-30{font-size:1.875rem!important}.font-size-xl-32{font-size:2rem!important}.font-size-xl-34{font-size:2.125rem!important}.font-size-xl-36{font-size:2.25rem!important}.font-size-xl-38{font-size:2.375rem!important}.font-size-xl-40{font-size:2.5rem!important}.font-size-xl-42{font-size:2.625rem!important}.font-size-xl-44{font-size:2.75rem!important}.font-size-xl-46{font-size:2.875rem!important}.font-size-xl-48{font-size:3rem!important}.font-size-xl-50{font-size:3.125rem!important}.font-size-xl-52{font-size:3.25rem!important}.font-size-xl-54{font-size:3.375rem!important}.font-size-xl-56{font-size:3.5rem!important}.font-size-xl-58{font-size:3.625rem!important}.font-size-xl-60{font-size:3.75rem!important}}.m-0{margin:0}.mt-0{margin-top:0}.mr-0{margin-right:0}.mb-0{margin-bottom:0}.ml-0,.mx-0{margin-left:0}.mx-0{margin-right:0}.my-0{margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0}.m-1{margin:2px}.mt-1{margin-top:2px}.mr-1{margin-right:2px}.mb-1{margin-bottom:2px}.ml-1,.mx-1{margin-left:2px}.mx-1{margin-right:2px}.my-1{margin-top:2px;margin-bottom:2px}.m-2{margin:4px}.mt-2{margin-top:4px}.mr-2{margin-right:4px}.mb-2{margin-bottom:4px}.ml-2,.mx-2{margin-left:4px}.mx-2{margin-right:4px}.my-2{margin-top:4px;margin-bottom:4px}.m-3{margin:8px}.mt-3{margin-top:8px}.mr-3{margin-right:8px}.mb-3{margin-bottom:8px}.ml-3,.mx-3{margin-left:8px}.mx-3{margin-right:8px}.my-3{margin-top:8px;margin-bottom:8px}.m-4{margin:12px}.mt-4{margin-top:12px}.mr-4{margin-right:12px}.mb-4{margin-bottom:12px}.ml-4,.mx-4{margin-left:12px}.mx-4{margin-right:12px}.my-4{margin-top:12px;margin-bottom:12px}.m-5{margin:16px}.mt-5{margin-top:16px}.mr-5{margin-right:16px}.mb-5{margin-bottom:16px}.ml-5,.mx-5{margin-left:16px}.mx-5{margin-right:16px}.my-5{margin-top:16px;margin-bottom:16px}.m-6{margin:24px}.mt-6{margin-top:24px}.mr-6{margin-right:24px}.mb-6{margin-bottom:24px}.ml-6,.mx-6{margin-left:24px}.mx-6{margin-right:24px}.my-6{margin-top:24px;margin-bottom:24px}.m-7{margin:32px}.mt-7{margin-top:32px}.mr-7{margin-right:32px}.mb-7{margin-bottom:32px}.ml-7,.mx-7{margin-left:32px}.mx-7{margin-right:32px}.my-7{margin-top:32px;margin-bottom:32px}.m-8{margin:40px}.mt-8{margin-top:40px}.mr-8{margin-right:40px}.mb-8{margin-bottom:40px}.ml-8,.mx-8{margin-left:40px}.mx-8{margin-right:40px}.my-8{margin-top:40px;margin-bottom:40px}.m-9{margin:48px}.mt-9{margin-top:48px}.mr-9{margin-right:48px}.mb-9{margin-bottom:48px}.ml-9,.mx-9{margin-left:48px}.mx-9{margin-right:48px}.my-9{margin-top:48px;margin-bottom:48px}.m-10{margin:56px}.mt-10{margin-top:56px}.mr-10{margin-right:56px}.mb-10{margin-bottom:56px}.ml-10,.mx-10{margin-left:56px}.mx-10{margin-right:56px}.my-10{margin-top:56px;margin-bottom:56px}.m-11{margin:64px}.mt-11{margin-top:64px}.mr-11{margin-right:64px}.mb-11{margin-bottom:64px}.ml-11,.mx-11{margin-left:64px}.mx-11{margin-right:64px}.my-11{margin-top:64px;margin-bottom:64px}.m-12{margin:80px}.mt-12{margin-top:80px}.mr-12{margin-right:80px}.mb-12{margin-bottom:80px}.ml-12,.mx-12{margin-left:80px}.mx-12{margin-right:80px}.my-12{margin-top:80px;margin-bottom:80px}.m-13{margin:96px}.mt-13{margin-top:96px}.mr-13{margin-right:96px}.mb-13{margin-bottom:96px}.ml-13,.mx-13{margin-left:96px}.mx-13{margin-right:96px}.my-13{margin-top:96px;margin-bottom:96px}.m-14{margin:112px}.mt-14{margin-top:112px}.mr-14{margin-right:112px}.mb-14{margin-bottom:112px}.ml-14,.mx-14{margin-left:112px}.mx-14{margin-right:112px}.my-14{margin-top:112px;margin-bottom:112px}.m-15{margin:128px}.mt-15{margin-top:128px}.mr-15{margin-right:128px}.mb-15{margin-bottom:128px}.ml-15,.mx-15{margin-left:128px}.mx-15{margin-right:128px}.my-15{margin-top:128px;margin-bottom:128px}.m-16{margin:192px}.mt-16{margin-top:192px}.mr-16{margin-right:192px}.mb-16{margin-bottom:192px}.ml-16,.mx-16{margin-left:192px}.mx-16{margin-right:192px}.my-16{margin-top:192px;margin-bottom:192px}.p-0{padding:0}.pt-0{padding-top:0}.pr-0{padding-right:0}.pb-0{padding-bottom:0}.pl-0,.px-0{padding-left:0}.px-0{padding-right:0}.py-0{padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0}.p-1{padding:2px}.pt-1{padding-top:2px}.pr-1{padding-right:2px}.pb-1{padding-bottom:2px}.pl-1,.px-1{padding-left:2px}.px-1{padding-right:2px}.py-1{padding-top:2px;padding-bottom:2px}.p-2{padding:4px}.pt-2{padding-top:4px}.pr-2{padding-right:4px}.pb-2{padding-bottom:4px}.pl-2,.px-2{padding-left:4px}.px-2{padding-right:4px}.py-2{padding-top:4px;padding-bottom:4px}.p-3{padding:8px}.pt-3{padding-top:8px}.pr-3{padding-right:8px}.pb-3{padding-bottom:8px}.pl-3,.px-3{padding-left:8px}.px-3{padding-right:8px}.py-3{padding-top:8px;padding-bottom:8px}.p-4{padding:12px}.pt-4{padding-top:12px}.pr-4{padding-right:12px}.pb-4{padding-bottom:12px}.pl-4,.px-4{padding-left:12px}.px-4{padding-right:12px}.py-4{padding-top:12px;padding-bottom:12px}.p-5{padding:16px}.pt-5{padding-top:16px}.pr-5{padding-right:16px}.pb-5{padding-bottom:16px}.pl-5,.px-5{padding-left:16px}.px-5{padding-right:16px}.py-5{padding-top:16px;padding-bottom:16px}.p-6{padding:24px}.pt-6{padding-top:24px}.pr-6{padding-right:24px}.pb-6{padding-bottom:24px}.pl-6,.px-6{padding-left:24px}.px-6{padding-right:24px}.py-6{padding-top:24px;padding-bottom:24px}.p-7{padding:32px}.pt-7{padding-top:32px}.pr-7{padding-right:32px}.pb-7{padding-bottom:32px}.pl-7,.px-7{padding-left:32px}.px-7{padding-right:32px}.py-7{padding-top:32px;padding-bottom:32px}.p-8{padding:40px}.pt-8{padding-top:40px}.pr-8{padding-right:40px}.pb-8{padding-bottom:40px}.pl-8,.px-8{padding-left:40px}.px-8{padding-right:40px}.py-8{padding-top:40px;padding-bottom:40px}.p-9{padding:48px}.pt-9{padding-top:48px}.pr-9{padding-right:48px}.pb-9{padding-bottom:48px}.pl-9,.px-9{padding-left:48px}.px-9{padding-right:48px}.py-9{padding-top:48px;padding-bottom:48px}.p-10{padding:56px}.pt-10{padding-top:56px}.pr-10{padding-right:56px}.pb-10{padding-bottom:56px}.pl-10,.px-10{padding-left:56px}.px-10{padding-right:56px}.py-10{padding-top:56px;padding-bottom:56px}.p-11{padding:64px}.pt-11{padding-top:64px}.pr-11{padding-right:64px}.pb-11{padding-bottom:64px}.pl-11,.px-11{padding-left:64px}.px-11{padding-right:64px}.py-11{padding-top:64px;padding-bottom:64px}.p-12{padding:80px}.pt-12{padding-top:80px}.pr-12{padding-right:80px}.pb-12{padding-bottom:80px}.pl-12,.px-12{padding-left:80px}.px-12{padding-right:80px}.py-12{padding-top:80px;padding-bottom:80px}.p-13{padding:96px}.pt-13{padding-top:96px}.pr-13{padding-right:96px}.pb-13{padding-bottom:96px}.pl-13,.px-13{padding-left:96px}.px-13{padding-right:96px}.py-13{padding-top:96px;padding-bottom:96px}.p-14{padding:112px}.pt-14{padding-top:112px}.pr-14{padding-right:112px}.pb-14{padding-bottom:112px}.pl-14,.px-14{padding-left:112px}.px-14{padding-right:112px}.py-14{padding-top:112px;padding-bottom:112px}.p-15{padding:128px}.pt-15{padding-top:128px}.pr-15{padding-right:128px}.pb-15{padding-bottom:128px}.pl-15,.px-15{padding-left:128px}.px-15{padding-right:128px}.py-15{padding-top:128px;padding-bottom:128px}.p-16{padding:192px}.pt-16{padding-top:192px}.pr-16{padding-right:192px}.pb-16{padding-bottom:192px}.pl-16,.px-16{padding-left:192px}.px-16{padding-right:192px}.py-16{padding-top:192px;padding-bottom:192px}.m-auto{margin:auto}.mt-auto{margin-top:auto}.mr-auto{margin-right:auto}.mb-auto{margin-bottom:auto}.ml-auto,.mx-auto{margin-left:auto}.mx-auto{margin-right:auto}.my-auto{margin-top:auto;margin-bottom:auto}@media(max-width:559px){.m-sm-0{margin:0}.mt-sm-0{margin-top:0}.mr-sm-0{margin-right:0}.mb-sm-0{margin-bottom:0}.ml-sm-0,.mx-sm-0{margin-left:0}.mx-sm-0{margin-right:0}.my-sm-0{margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0}.m-sm-1{margin:2px}.mt-sm-1{margin-top:2px}.mr-sm-1{margin-right:2px}.mb-sm-1{margin-bottom:2px}.ml-sm-1,.mx-sm-1{margin-left:2px}.mx-sm-1{margin-right:2px}.my-sm-1{margin-top:2px;margin-bottom:2px}.m-sm-2{margin:4px}.mt-sm-2{margin-top:4px}.mr-sm-2{margin-right:4px}.mb-sm-2{margin-bottom:4px}.ml-sm-2,.mx-sm-2{margin-left:4px}.mx-sm-2{margin-right:4px}.my-sm-2{margin-top:4px;margin-bottom:4px}.m-sm-3{margin:8px}.mt-sm-3{margin-top:8px}.mr-sm-3{margin-right:8px}.mb-sm-3{margin-bottom:8px}.ml-sm-3,.mx-sm-3{margin-left:8px}.mx-sm-3{margin-right:8px}.my-sm-3{margin-top:8px;margin-bottom:8px}.m-sm-4{margin:12px}.mt-sm-4{margin-top:12px}.mr-sm-4{margin-right:12px}.mb-sm-4{margin-bottom:12px}.ml-sm-4,.mx-sm-4{margin-left:12px}.mx-sm-4{margin-right:12px}.my-sm-4{margin-top:12px;margin-bottom:12px}.m-sm-5{margin:16px}.mt-sm-5{margin-top:16px}.mr-sm-5{margin-right:16px}.mb-sm-5{margin-bottom:16px}.ml-sm-5,.mx-sm-5{margin-left:16px}.mx-sm-5{margin-right:16px}.my-sm-5{margin-top:16px;margin-bottom:16px}.m-sm-6{margin:24px}.mt-sm-6{margin-top:24px}.mr-sm-6{margin-right:24px}.mb-sm-6{margin-bottom:24px}.ml-sm-6,.mx-sm-6{margin-left:24px}.mx-sm-6{margin-right:24px}.my-sm-6{margin-top:24px;margin-bottom:24px}.m-sm-7{margin:32px}.mt-sm-7{margin-top:32px}.mr-sm-7{margin-right:32px}.mb-sm-7{margin-bottom:32px}.ml-sm-7,.mx-sm-7{margin-left:32px}.mx-sm-7{margin-right:32px}.my-sm-7{margin-top:32px;margin-bottom:32px}.m-sm-8{margin:40px}.mt-sm-8{margin-top:40px}.mr-sm-8{margin-right:40px}.mb-sm-8{margin-bottom:40px}.ml-sm-8,.mx-sm-8{margin-left:40px}.mx-sm-8{margin-right:40px}.my-sm-8{margin-top:40px;margin-bottom:40px}.m-sm-9{margin:48px}.mt-sm-9{margin-top:48px}.mr-sm-9{margin-right:48px}.mb-sm-9{margin-bottom:48px}.ml-sm-9,.mx-sm-9{margin-left:48px}.mx-sm-9{margin-right:48px}.my-sm-9{margin-top:48px;margin-bottom:48px}.m-sm-10{margin:56px}.mt-sm-10{margin-top:56px}.mr-sm-10{margin-right:56px}.mb-sm-10{margin-bottom:56px}.ml-sm-10,.mx-sm-10{margin-left:56px}.mx-sm-10{margin-right:56px}.my-sm-10{margin-top:56px;margin-bottom:56px}.m-sm-11{margin:64px}.mt-sm-11{margin-top:64px}.mr-sm-11{margin-right:64px}.mb-sm-11{margin-bottom:64px}.ml-sm-11,.mx-sm-11{margin-left:64px}.mx-sm-11{margin-right:64px}.my-sm-11{margin-top:64px;margin-bottom:64px}.m-sm-12{margin:80px}.mt-sm-12{margin-top:80px}.mr-sm-12{margin-right:80px}.mb-sm-12{margin-bottom:80px}.ml-sm-12,.mx-sm-12{margin-left:80px}.mx-sm-12{margin-right:80px}.my-sm-12{margin-top:80px;margin-bottom:80px}.m-sm-13{margin:96px}.mt-sm-13{margin-top:96px}.mr-sm-13{margin-right:96px}.mb-sm-13{margin-bottom:96px}.ml-sm-13,.mx-sm-13{margin-left:96px}.mx-sm-13{margin-right:96px}.my-sm-13{margin-top:96px;margin-bottom:96px}.m-sm-14{margin:112px}.mt-sm-14{margin-top:112px}.mr-sm-14{margin-right:112px}.mb-sm-14{margin-bottom:112px}.ml-sm-14,.mx-sm-14{margin-left:112px}.mx-sm-14{margin-right:112px}.my-sm-14{margin-top:112px;margin-bottom:112px}.m-sm-15{margin:128px}.mt-sm-15{margin-top:128px}.mr-sm-15{margin-right:128px}.mb-sm-15{margin-bottom:128px}.ml-sm-15,.mx-sm-15{margin-left:128px}.mx-sm-15{margin-right:128px}.my-sm-15{margin-top:128px;margin-bottom:128px}.m-sm-16{margin:192px}.mt-sm-16{margin-top:192px}.mr-sm-16{margin-right:192px}.mb-sm-16{margin-bottom:192px}.ml-sm-16,.mx-sm-16{margin-left:192px}.mx-sm-16{margin-right:192px}.my-sm-16{margin-top:192px;margin-bottom:192px}.p-sm-0{padding:0}.pt-sm-0{padding-top:0}.pr-sm-0{padding-right:0}.pb-sm-0{padding-bottom:0}.pl-sm-0,.px-sm-0{padding-left:0}.px-sm-0{padding-right:0}.py-sm-0{padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0}.p-sm-1{padding:2px}.pt-sm-1{padding-top:2px}.pr-sm-1{padding-right:2px}.pb-sm-1{padding-bottom:2px}.pl-sm-1,.px-sm-1{padding-left:2px}.px-sm-1{padding-right:2px}.py-sm-1{padding-top:2px;padding-bottom:2px}.p-sm-2{padding:4px}.pt-sm-2{padding-top:4px}.pr-sm-2{padding-right:4px}.pb-sm-2{padding-bottom:4px}.pl-sm-2,.px-sm-2{padding-left:4px}.px-sm-2{padding-right:4px}.py-sm-2{padding-top:4px;padding-bottom:4px}.p-sm-3{padding:8px}.pt-sm-3{padding-top:8px}.pr-sm-3{padding-right:8px}.pb-sm-3{padding-bottom:8px}.pl-sm-3,.px-sm-3{padding-left:8px}.px-sm-3{padding-right:8px}.py-sm-3{padding-top:8px;padding-bottom:8px}.p-sm-4{padding:12px}.pt-sm-4{padding-top:12px}.pr-sm-4{padding-right:12px}.pb-sm-4{padding-bottom:12px}.pl-sm-4,.px-sm-4{padding-left:12px}.px-sm-4{padding-right:12px}.py-sm-4{padding-top:12px;padding-bottom:12px}.p-sm-5{padding:16px}.pt-sm-5{padding-top:16px}.pr-sm-5{padding-right:16px}.pb-sm-5{padding-bottom:16px}.pl-sm-5,.px-sm-5{padding-left:16px}.px-sm-5{padding-right:16px}.py-sm-5{padding-top:16px;padding-bottom:16px}.p-sm-6{padding:24px}.pt-sm-6{padding-top:24px}.pr-sm-6{padding-right:24px}.pb-sm-6{padding-bottom:24px}.pl-sm-6,.px-sm-6{padding-left:24px}.px-sm-6{padding-right:24px}.py-sm-6{padding-top:24px;padding-bottom:24px}.p-sm-7{padding:32px}.pt-sm-7{padding-top:32px}.pr-sm-7{padding-right:32px}.pb-sm-7{padding-bottom:32px}.pl-sm-7,.px-sm-7{padding-left:32px}.px-sm-7{padding-right:32px}.py-sm-7{padding-top:32px;padding-bottom:32px}.p-sm-8{padding:40px}.pt-sm-8{padding-top:40px}.pr-sm-8{padding-right:40px}.pb-sm-8{padding-bottom:40px}.pl-sm-8,.px-sm-8{padding-left:40px}.px-sm-8{padding-right:40px}.py-sm-8{padding-top:40px;padding-bottom:40px}.p-sm-9{padding:48px}.pt-sm-9{padding-top:48px}.pr-sm-9{padding-right:48px}.pb-sm-9{padding-bottom:48px}.pl-sm-9,.px-sm-9{padding-left:48px}.px-sm-9{padding-right:48px}.py-sm-9{padding-top:48px;padding-bottom:48px}.p-sm-10{padding:56px}.pt-sm-10{padding-top:56px}.pr-sm-10{padding-right:56px}.pb-sm-10{padding-bottom:56px}.pl-sm-10,.px-sm-10{padding-left:56px}.px-sm-10{padding-right:56px}.py-sm-10{padding-top:56px;padding-bottom:56px}.p-sm-11{padding:64px}.pt-sm-11{padding-top:64px}.pr-sm-11{padding-right:64px}.pb-sm-11{padding-bottom:64px}.pl-sm-11,.px-sm-11{padding-left:64px}.px-sm-11{padding-right:64px}.py-sm-11{padding-top:64px;padding-bottom:64px}.p-sm-12{padding:80px}.pt-sm-12{padding-top:80px}.pr-sm-12{padding-right:80px}.pb-sm-12{padding-bottom:80px}.pl-sm-12,.px-sm-12{padding-left:80px}.px-sm-12{padding-right:80px}.py-sm-12{padding-top:80px;padding-bottom:80px}.p-sm-13{padding:96px}.pt-sm-13{padding-top:96px}.pr-sm-13{padding-right:96px}.pb-sm-13{padding-bottom:96px}.pl-sm-13,.px-sm-13{padding-left:96px}.px-sm-13{padding-right:96px}.py-sm-13{padding-top:96px;padding-bottom:96px}.p-sm-14{padding:112px}.pt-sm-14{padding-top:112px}.pr-sm-14{padding-right:112px}.pb-sm-14{padding-bottom:112px}.pl-sm-14,.px-sm-14{padding-left:112px}.px-sm-14{padding-right:112px}.py-sm-14{padding-top:112px;padding-bottom:112px}.p-sm-15{padding:128px}.pt-sm-15{padding-top:128px}.pr-sm-15{padding-right:128px}.pb-sm-15{padding-bottom:128px}.pl-sm-15,.px-sm-15{padding-left:128px}.px-sm-15{padding-right:128px}.py-sm-15{padding-top:128px;padding-bottom:128px}.p-sm-16{padding:192px}.pt-sm-16{padding-top:192px}.pr-sm-16{padding-right:192px}.pb-sm-16{padding-bottom:192px}.pl-sm-16,.px-sm-16{padding-left:192px}.px-sm-16{padding-right:192px}.py-sm-16{padding-top:192px;padding-bottom:192px}.m-sm-auto{margin:auto}.mt-sm-auto{margin-top:auto}.mr-sm-auto{margin-right:auto}.mb-sm-auto{margin-bottom:auto}.ml-sm-auto,.mx-sm-auto{margin-left:auto}.mx-sm-auto{margin-right:auto}.my-sm-auto{margin-top:auto;margin-bottom:auto}}@media(min-width:960px){.m-md-0{margin:0}.mt-md-0{margin-top:0}.mr-md-0{margin-right:0}.mb-md-0{margin-bottom:0}.ml-md-0,.mx-md-0{margin-left:0}.mx-md-0{margin-right:0}.my-md-0{margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0}.m-md-1{margin:2px}.mt-md-1{margin-top:2px}.mr-md-1{margin-right:2px}.mb-md-1{margin-bottom:2px}.ml-md-1,.mx-md-1{margin-left:2px}.mx-md-1{margin-right:2px}.my-md-1{margin-top:2px;margin-bottom:2px}.m-md-2{margin:4px}.mt-md-2{margin-top:4px}.mr-md-2{margin-right:4px}.mb-md-2{margin-bottom:4px}.ml-md-2,.mx-md-2{margin-left:4px}.mx-md-2{margin-right:4px}.my-md-2{margin-top:4px;margin-bottom:4px}.m-md-3{margin:8px}.mt-md-3{margin-top:8px}.mr-md-3{margin-right:8px}.mb-md-3{margin-bottom:8px}.ml-md-3,.mx-md-3{margin-left:8px}.mx-md-3{margin-right:8px}.my-md-3{margin-top:8px;margin-bottom:8px}.m-md-4{margin:12px}.mt-md-4{margin-top:12px}.mr-md-4{margin-right:12px}.mb-md-4{margin-bottom:12px}.ml-md-4,.mx-md-4{margin-left:12px}.mx-md-4{margin-right:12px}.my-md-4{margin-top:12px;margin-bottom:12px}.m-md-5{margin:16px}.mt-md-5{margin-top:16px}.mr-md-5{margin-right:16px}.mb-md-5{margin-bottom:16px}.ml-md-5,.mx-md-5{margin-left:16px}.mx-md-5{margin-right:16px}.my-md-5{margin-top:16px;margin-bottom:16px}.m-md-6{margin:24px}.mt-md-6{margin-top:24px}.mr-md-6{margin-right:24px}.mb-md-6{margin-bottom:24px}.ml-md-6,.mx-md-6{margin-left:24px}.mx-md-6{margin-right:24px}.my-md-6{margin-top:24px;margin-bottom:24px}.m-md-7{margin:32px}.mt-md-7{margin-top:32px}.mr-md-7{margin-right:32px}.mb-md-7{margin-bottom:32px}.ml-md-7,.mx-md-7{margin-left:32px}.mx-md-7{margin-right:32px}.my-md-7{margin-top:32px;margin-bottom:32px}.m-md-8{margin:40px}.mt-md-8{margin-top:40px}.mr-md-8{margin-right:40px}.mb-md-8{margin-bottom:40px}.ml-md-8,.mx-md-8{margin-left:40px}.mx-md-8{margin-right:40px}.my-md-8{margin-top:40px;margin-bottom:40px}.m-md-9{margin:48px}.mt-md-9{margin-top:48px}.mr-md-9{margin-right:48px}.mb-md-9{margin-bottom:48px}.ml-md-9,.mx-md-9{margin-left:48px}.mx-md-9{margin-right:48px}.my-md-9{margin-top:48px;margin-bottom:48px}.m-md-10{margin:56px}.mt-md-10{margin-top:56px}.mr-md-10{margin-right:56px}.mb-md-10{margin-bottom:56px}.ml-md-10,.mx-md-10{margin-left:56px}.mx-md-10{margin-right:56px}.my-md-10{margin-top:56px;margin-bottom:56px}.m-md-11{margin:64px}.mt-md-11{margin-top:64px}.mr-md-11{margin-right:64px}.mb-md-11{margin-bottom:64px}.ml-md-11,.mx-md-11{margin-left:64px}.mx-md-11{margin-right:64px}.my-md-11{margin-top:64px;margin-bottom:64px}.m-md-12{margin:80px}.mt-md-12{margin-top:80px}.mr-md-12{margin-right:80px}.mb-md-12{margin-bottom:80px}.ml-md-12,.mx-md-12{margin-left:80px}.mx-md-12{margin-right:80px}.my-md-12{margin-top:80px;margin-bottom:80px}.m-md-13{margin:96px}.mt-md-13{margin-top:96px}.mr-md-13{margin-right:96px}.mb-md-13{margin-bottom:96px}.ml-md-13,.mx-md-13{margin-left:96px}.mx-md-13{margin-right:96px}.my-md-13{margin-top:96px;margin-bottom:96px}.m-md-14{margin:112px}.mt-md-14{margin-top:112px}.mr-md-14{margin-right:112px}.mb-md-14{margin-bottom:112px}.ml-md-14,.mx-md-14{margin-left:112px}.mx-md-14{margin-right:112px}.my-md-14{margin-top:112px;margin-bottom:112px}.m-md-15{margin:128px}.mt-md-15{margin-top:128px}.mr-md-15{margin-right:128px}.mb-md-15{margin-bottom:128px}.ml-md-15,.mx-md-15{margin-left:128px}.mx-md-15{margin-right:128px}.my-md-15{margin-top:128px;margin-bottom:128px}.m-md-16{margin:192px}.mt-md-16{margin-top:192px}.mr-md-16{margin-right:192px}.mb-md-16{margin-bottom:192px}.ml-md-16,.mx-md-16{margin-left:192px}.mx-md-16{margin-right:192px}.my-md-16{margin-top:192px;margin-bottom:192px}.p-md-0{padding:0}.pt-md-0{padding-top:0}.pr-md-0{padding-right:0}.pb-md-0{padding-bottom:0}.pl-md-0,.px-md-0{padding-left:0}.px-md-0{padding-right:0}.py-md-0{padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0}.p-md-1{padding:2px}.pt-md-1{padding-top:2px}.pr-md-1{padding-right:2px}.pb-md-1{padding-bottom:2px}.pl-md-1,.px-md-1{padding-left:2px}.px-md-1{padding-right:2px}.py-md-1{padding-top:2px;padding-bottom:2px}.p-md-2{padding:4px}.pt-md-2{padding-top:4px}.pr-md-2{padding-right:4px}.pb-md-2{padding-bottom:4px}.pl-md-2,.px-md-2{padding-left:4px}.px-md-2{padding-right:4px}.py-md-2{padding-top:4px;padding-bottom:4px}.p-md-3{padding:8px}.pt-md-3{padding-top:8px}.pr-md-3{padding-right:8px}.pb-md-3{padding-bottom:8px}.pl-md-3,.px-md-3{padding-left:8px}.px-md-3{padding-right:8px}.py-md-3{padding-top:8px;padding-bottom:8px}.p-md-4{padding:12px}.pt-md-4{padding-top:12px}.pr-md-4{padding-right:12px}.pb-md-4{padding-bottom:12px}.pl-md-4,.px-md-4{padding-left:12px}.px-md-4{padding-right:12px}.py-md-4{padding-top:12px;padding-bottom:12px}.p-md-5{padding:16px}.pt-md-5{padding-top:16px}.pr-md-5{padding-right:16px}.pb-md-5{padding-bottom:16px}.pl-md-5,.px-md-5{padding-left:16px}.px-md-5{padding-right:16px}.py-md-5{padding-top:16px;padding-bottom:16px}.p-md-6{padding:24px}.pt-md-6{padding-top:24px}.pr-md-6{padding-right:24px}.pb-md-6{padding-bottom:24px}.pl-md-6,.px-md-6{padding-left:24px}.px-md-6{padding-right:24px}.py-md-6{padding-top:24px;padding-bottom:24px}.p-md-7{padding:32px}.pt-md-7{padding-top:32px}.pr-md-7{padding-right:32px}.pb-md-7{padding-bottom:32px}.pl-md-7,.px-md-7{padding-left:32px}.px-md-7{padding-right:32px}.py-md-7{padding-top:32px;padding-bottom:32px}.p-md-8{padding:40px}.pt-md-8{padding-top:40px}.pr-md-8{padding-right:40px}.pb-md-8{padding-bottom:40px}.pl-md-8,.px-md-8{padding-left:40px}.px-md-8{padding-right:40px}.py-md-8{padding-top:40px;padding-bottom:40px}.p-md-9{padding:48px}.pt-md-9{padding-top:48px}.pr-md-9{padding-right:48px}.pb-md-9{padding-bottom:48px}.pl-md-9,.px-md-9{padding-left:48px}.px-md-9{padding-right:48px}.py-md-9{padding-top:48px;padding-bottom:48px}.p-md-10{padding:56px}.pt-md-10{padding-top:56px}.pr-md-10{padding-right:56px}.pb-md-10{padding-bottom:56px}.pl-md-10,.px-md-10{padding-left:56px}.px-md-10{padding-right:56px}.py-md-10{padding-top:56px;padding-bottom:56px}.p-md-11{padding:64px}.pt-md-11{padding-top:64px}.pr-md-11{padding-right:64px}.pb-md-11{padding-bottom:64px}.pl-md-11,.px-md-11{padding-left:64px}.px-md-11{padding-right:64px}.py-md-11{padding-top:64px;padding-bottom:64px}.p-md-12{padding:80px}.pt-md-12{padding-top:80px}.pr-md-12{padding-right:80px}.pb-md-12{padding-bottom:80px}.pl-md-12,.px-md-12{padding-left:80px}.px-md-12{padding-right:80px}.py-md-12{padding-top:80px;padding-bottom:80px}.p-md-13{padding:96px}.pt-md-13{padding-top:96px}.pr-md-13{padding-right:96px}.pb-md-13{padding-bottom:96px}.pl-md-13,.px-md-13{padding-left:96px}.px-md-13{padding-right:96px}.py-md-13{padding-top:96px;padding-bottom:96px}.p-md-14{padding:112px}.pt-md-14{padding-top:112px}.pr-md-14{padding-right:112px}.pb-md-14{padding-bottom:112px}.pl-md-14,.px-md-14{padding-left:112px}.px-md-14{padding-right:112px}.py-md-14{padding-top:112px;padding-bottom:112px}.p-md-15{padding:128px}.pt-md-15{padding-top:128px}.pr-md-15{padding-right:128px}.pb-md-15{padding-bottom:128px}.pl-md-15,.px-md-15{padding-left:128px}.px-md-15{padding-right:128px}.py-md-15{padding-top:128px;padding-bottom:128px}.p-md-16{padding:192px}.pt-md-16{padding-top:192px}.pr-md-16{padding-right:192px}.pb-md-16{padding-bottom:192px}.pl-md-16,.px-md-16{padding-left:192px}.px-md-16{padding-right:192px}.py-md-16{padding-top:192px;padding-bottom:192px}.m-md-auto{margin:auto}.mt-md-auto{margin-top:auto}.mr-md-auto{margin-right:auto}.mb-md-auto{margin-bottom:auto}.ml-md-auto,.mx-md-auto{margin-left:auto}.mx-md-auto{margin-right:auto}.my-md-auto{margin-top:auto;margin-bottom:auto}}@media(min-width:1264px){.m-lg-0{margin:0}.mt-lg-0{margin-top:0}.mr-lg-0{margin-right:0}.mb-lg-0{margin-bottom:0}.ml-lg-0,.mx-lg-0{margin-left:0}.mx-lg-0{margin-right:0}.my-lg-0{margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0}.m-lg-1{margin:2px}.mt-lg-1{margin-top:2px}.mr-lg-1{margin-right:2px}.mb-lg-1{margin-bottom:2px}.ml-lg-1,.mx-lg-1{margin-left:2px}.mx-lg-1{margin-right:2px}.my-lg-1{margin-top:2px;margin-bottom:2px}.m-lg-2{margin:4px}.mt-lg-2{margin-top:4px}.mr-lg-2{margin-right:4px}.mb-lg-2{margin-bottom:4px}.ml-lg-2,.mx-lg-2{margin-left:4px}.mx-lg-2{margin-right:4px}.my-lg-2{margin-top:4px;margin-bottom:4px}.m-lg-3{margin:8px}.mt-lg-3{margin-top:8px}.mr-lg-3{margin-right:8px}.mb-lg-3{margin-bottom:8px}.ml-lg-3,.mx-lg-3{margin-left:8px}.mx-lg-3{margin-right:8px}.my-lg-3{margin-top:8px;margin-bottom:8px}.m-lg-4{margin:12px}.mt-lg-4{margin-top:12px}.mr-lg-4{margin-right:12px}.mb-lg-4{margin-bottom:12px}.ml-lg-4,.mx-lg-4{margin-left:12px}.mx-lg-4{margin-right:12px}.my-lg-4{margin-top:12px;margin-bottom:12px}.m-lg-5{margin:16px}.mt-lg-5{margin-top:16px}.mr-lg-5{margin-right:16px}.mb-lg-5{margin-bottom:16px}.ml-lg-5,.mx-lg-5{margin-left:16px}.mx-lg-5{margin-right:16px}.my-lg-5{margin-top:16px;margin-bottom:16px}.m-lg-6{margin:24px}.mt-lg-6{margin-top:24px}.mr-lg-6{margin-right:24px}.mb-lg-6{margin-bottom:24px}.ml-lg-6,.mx-lg-6{margin-left:24px}.mx-lg-6{margin-right:24px}.my-lg-6{margin-top:24px;margin-bottom:24px}.m-lg-7{margin:32px}.mt-lg-7{margin-top:32px}.mr-lg-7{margin-right:32px}.mb-lg-7{margin-bottom:32px}.ml-lg-7,.mx-lg-7{margin-left:32px}.mx-lg-7{margin-right:32px}.my-lg-7{margin-top:32px;margin-bottom:32px}.m-lg-8{margin:40px}.mt-lg-8{margin-top:40px}.mr-lg-8{margin-right:40px}.mb-lg-8{margin-bottom:40px}.ml-lg-8,.mx-lg-8{margin-left:40px}.mx-lg-8{margin-right:40px}.my-lg-8{margin-top:40px;margin-bottom:40px}.m-lg-9{margin:48px}.mt-lg-9{margin-top:48px}.mr-lg-9{margin-right:48px}.mb-lg-9{margin-bottom:48px}.ml-lg-9,.mx-lg-9{margin-left:48px}.mx-lg-9{margin-right:48px}.my-lg-9{margin-top:48px;margin-bottom:48px}.m-lg-10{margin:56px}.mt-lg-10{margin-top:56px}.mr-lg-10{margin-right:56px}.mb-lg-10{margin-bottom:56px}.ml-lg-10,.mx-lg-10{margin-left:56px}.mx-lg-10{margin-right:56px}.my-lg-10{margin-top:56px;margin-bottom:56px}.m-lg-11{margin:64px}.mt-lg-11{margin-top:64px}.mr-lg-11{margin-right:64px}.mb-lg-11{margin-bottom:64px}.ml-lg-11,.mx-lg-11{margin-left:64px}.mx-lg-11{margin-right:64px}.my-lg-11{margin-top:64px;margin-bottom:64px}.m-lg-12{margin:80px}.mt-lg-12{margin-top:80px}.mr-lg-12{margin-right:80px}.mb-lg-12{margin-bottom:80px}.ml-lg-12,.mx-lg-12{margin-left:80px}.mx-lg-12{margin-right:80px}.my-lg-12{margin-top:80px;margin-bottom:80px}.m-lg-13{margin:96px}.mt-lg-13{margin-top:96px}.mr-lg-13{margin-right:96px}.mb-lg-13{margin-bottom:96px}.ml-lg-13,.mx-lg-13{margin-left:96px}.mx-lg-13{margin-right:96px}.my-lg-13{margin-top:96px;margin-bottom:96px}.m-lg-14{margin:112px}.mt-lg-14{margin-top:112px}.mr-lg-14{margin-right:112px}.mb-lg-14{margin-bottom:112px}.ml-lg-14,.mx-lg-14{margin-left:112px}.mx-lg-14{margin-right:112px}.my-lg-14{margin-top:112px;margin-bottom:112px}.m-lg-15{margin:128px}.mt-lg-15{margin-top:128px}.mr-lg-15{margin-right:128px}.mb-lg-15{margin-bottom:128px}.ml-lg-15,.mx-lg-15{margin-left:128px}.mx-lg-15{margin-right:128px}.my-lg-15{margin-top:128px;margin-bottom:128px}.m-lg-16{margin:192px}.mt-lg-16{margin-top:192px}.mr-lg-16{margin-right:192px}.mb-lg-16{margin-bottom:192px}.ml-lg-16,.mx-lg-16{margin-left:192px}.mx-lg-16{margin-right:192px}.my-lg-16{margin-top:192px;margin-bottom:192px}.p-lg-0{padding:0}.pt-lg-0{padding-top:0}.pr-lg-0{padding-right:0}.pb-lg-0{padding-bottom:0}.pl-lg-0,.px-lg-0{padding-left:0}.px-lg-0{padding-right:0}.py-lg-0{padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0}.p-lg-1{padding:2px}.pt-lg-1{padding-top:2px}.pr-lg-1{padding-right:2px}.pb-lg-1{padding-bottom:2px}.pl-lg-1,.px-lg-1{padding-left:2px}.px-lg-1{padding-right:2px}.py-lg-1{padding-top:2px;padding-bottom:2px}.p-lg-2{padding:4px}.pt-lg-2{padding-top:4px}.pr-lg-2{padding-right:4px}.pb-lg-2{padding-bottom:4px}.pl-lg-2,.px-lg-2{padding-left:4px}.px-lg-2{padding-right:4px}.py-lg-2{padding-top:4px;padding-bottom:4px}.p-lg-3{padding:8px}.pt-lg-3{padding-top:8px}.pr-lg-3{padding-right:8px}.pb-lg-3{padding-bottom:8px}.pl-lg-3,.px-lg-3{padding-left:8px}.px-lg-3{padding-right:8px}.py-lg-3{padding-top:8px;padding-bottom:8px}.p-lg-4{padding:12px}.pt-lg-4{padding-top:12px}.pr-lg-4{padding-right:12px}.pb-lg-4{padding-bottom:12px}.pl-lg-4,.px-lg-4{padding-left:12px}.px-lg-4{padding-right:12px}.py-lg-4{padding-top:12px;padding-bottom:12px}.p-lg-5{padding:16px}.pt-lg-5{padding-top:16px}.pr-lg-5{padding-right:16px}.pb-lg-5{padding-bottom:16px}.pl-lg-5,.px-lg-5{padding-left:16px}.px-lg-5{padding-right:16px}.py-lg-5{padding-top:16px;padding-bottom:16px}.p-lg-6{padding:24px}.pt-lg-6{padding-top:24px}.pr-lg-6{padding-right:24px}.pb-lg-6{padding-bottom:24px}.pl-lg-6,.px-lg-6{padding-left:24px}.px-lg-6{padding-right:24px}.py-lg-6{padding-top:24px;padding-bottom:24px}.p-lg-7{padding:32px}.pt-lg-7{padding-top:32px}.pr-lg-7{padding-right:32px}.pb-lg-7{padding-bottom:32px}.pl-lg-7,.px-lg-7{padding-left:32px}.px-lg-7{padding-right:32px}.py-lg-7{padding-top:32px;padding-bottom:32px}.p-lg-8{padding:40px}.pt-lg-8{padding-top:40px}.pr-lg-8{padding-right:40px}.pb-lg-8{padding-bottom:40px}.pl-lg-8,.px-lg-8{padding-left:40px}.px-lg-8{padding-right:40px}.py-lg-8{padding-top:40px;padding-bottom:40px}.p-lg-9{padding:48px}.pt-lg-9{padding-top:48px}.pr-lg-9{padding-right:48px}.pb-lg-9{padding-bottom:48px}.pl-lg-9,.px-lg-9{padding-left:48px}.px-lg-9{padding-right:48px}.py-lg-9{padding-top:48px;padding-bottom:48px}.p-lg-10{padding:56px}.pt-lg-10{padding-top:56px}.pr-lg-10{padding-right:56px}.pb-lg-10{padding-bottom:56px}.pl-lg-10,.px-lg-10{padding-left:56px}.px-lg-10{padding-right:56px}.py-lg-10{padding-top:56px;padding-bottom:56px}.p-lg-11{padding:64px}.pt-lg-11{padding-top:64px}.pr-lg-11{padding-right:64px}.pb-lg-11{padding-bottom:64px}.pl-lg-11,.px-lg-11{padding-left:64px}.px-lg-11{padding-right:64px}.py-lg-11{padding-top:64px;padding-bottom:64px}.p-lg-12{padding:80px}.pt-lg-12{padding-top:80px}.pr-lg-12{padding-right:80px}.pb-lg-12{padding-bottom:80px}.pl-lg-12,.px-lg-12{padding-left:80px}.px-lg-12{padding-right:80px}.py-lg-12{padding-top:80px;padding-bottom:80px}.p-lg-13{padding:96px}.pt-lg-13{padding-top:96px}.pr-lg-13{padding-right:96px}.pb-lg-13{padding-bottom:96px}.pl-lg-13,.px-lg-13{padding-left:96px}.px-lg-13{padding-right:96px}.py-lg-13{padding-top:96px;padding-bottom:96px}.p-lg-14{padding:112px}.pt-lg-14{padding-top:112px}.pr-lg-14{padding-right:112px}.pb-lg-14{padding-bottom:112px}.pl-lg-14,.px-lg-14{padding-left:112px}.px-lg-14{padding-right:112px}.py-lg-14{padding-top:112px;padding-bottom:112px}.p-lg-15{padding:128px}.pt-lg-15{padding-top:128px}.pr-lg-15{padding-right:128px}.pb-lg-15{padding-bottom:128px}.pl-lg-15,.px-lg-15{padding-left:128px}.px-lg-15{padding-right:128px}.py-lg-15{padding-top:128px;padding-bottom:128px}.p-lg-16{padding:192px}.pt-lg-16{padding-top:192px}.pr-lg-16{padding-right:192px}.pb-lg-16{padding-bottom:192px}.pl-lg-16,.px-lg-16{padding-left:192px}.px-lg-16{padding-right:192px}.py-lg-16{padding-top:192px;padding-bottom:192px}.m-lg-auto{margin:auto}.mt-lg-auto{margin-top:auto}.mr-lg-auto{margin-right:auto}.mb-lg-auto{margin-bottom:auto}.ml-lg-auto,.mx-lg-auto{margin-left:auto}.mx-lg-auto{margin-right:auto}.my-lg-auto{margin-top:auto;margin-bottom:auto}}.story__text{font-size:14px}.story__text-wrap{padding:12px;max-height:400px;overflow-y:auto;border:2px solid #ff470f;border-radius:4px}.story .highlight{font-style:normal;background-color:rgba(72,199,116,.6)}.question{margin-bottom:8px;padding:12px 16px!important}.question.class-0{border-left:4px solid #ff470f}.question.class-1{border-left:4px solid #48c774}.question.class-2{border-left:4px solid #ffdd57}.question .v-card__text{padding:0!important}.question .v-chip{margin:0 8px 4px 0}",""]),e.exports=t},421:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var r=n(13),o=n(80),d=n(401),l=(n(20),n(37),n(38),n(35),n(36),n(15),n(21),n(22),n(7),n(83),n(181),n(48),n(41),n(134));function h(e,t){var n;if("undefined"==typeof Symbol||null==e[Symbol.iterator]){if(Array.isArray(e)||(n=function(e,t){if(!e)return;if("string"==typeof e)return c(e,t);var n=Object.prototype.toString.call(e).slice(8,-1);"Object"===n&&e.constructor&&(n=e.constructor.name);if("Map"===n||"Set"===n)return Array.from(e);if("Arguments"===n||/^(?:Ui|I)nt(?:8|16|32)(?:Clamped)?Array$/.test(n))return c(e,t)}(e))||t&&e&&"number"==typeof e.length){n&&(e=n);var i=0;return function(){return i>=e.length?{done:!0}:{done:!1,value:e[i++]}}}throw new TypeError("Invalid attempt to iterate non-iterable instance.\nIn order to be iterable, non-array objects must have a [Symbol.iterator]() method.")}return(n=e[Symbol.iterator]()).next.bind(n)}function c(e,t){(null==t||t>e.length)&&(t=e.length);for(var i=0,n=new Array(t);i<t;i++)n[i]=e[i];return n}var m=function(e,t,n,desc){var r,o=arguments.length,d=o<3?t:null===desc?desc=Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(t,n):desc;if("object"==typeof Reflect&&"function"==typeof Reflect.decorate)d=Reflect.decorate(e,t,n,desc);else for(var i=e.length-1;i>=0;i--)(r=e[i])&&(d=(o<3?r(d):o>3?r(t,n,d):r(t,n))||d);return o>3&&d&&Object.defineProperty(t,n,d),d},f=function(e){function t(){var t;return(t=e.apply(this,arguments)||this).ans="",t.isPred=!1,t}Object(r.a)(t,e);var n=t.prototype;return n.extractQuestionAns=function(e){for(var t,n=[],r=h(e.split("|"));!(t=r()).done;){var source=t.value;if("None"!==source)for(var o,d=h(source.split(","));!(o=d()).done;){var l=o.value.split(":");n.push(this.story.story_text.substring(l[0],l[1]))}}return n},n.clickChip=function(e,t){void 0===t&&(t=!1),this.ans=e.trim(),this.isPred=t},Object(l.a)(t,[{key:"storyId",get:function(){return this.story.story_id.replace("./cnn/stories/","")}},{key:"text",get:function(){var e=this,t=this.story.story_text.replace(/\n/g,"<br>");if(this.ans){if(this.isPred){var n=new RegExp(this.ans,"i"),r=t.match(n);this.ans=r?r[0]:this.ans}t=t.replace(this.ans,'<em class="highlight">'+this.ans+"</em>"),setTimeout((function(){var t=document.getElementById(e.storyId);if(t){var n=t.querySelector("p"),r=t.querySelector(".highlight");if(r&&n){var o=n.getBoundingClientRect(),d=r.getBoundingClientRect();t.scrollTop=d.y-o.y,t.scrollIntoView(),t.scrollTop-=64}}}),200)}return t}},{key:"extractAns",get:function(){for(var e,t=[],n=h(this.story.questions);!(e=n()).done;){var q=e.value;t.push(this.extractQuestionAns(q.answer_char_ranges))}return t}}]),t}(o.Vue);m([Object(o.Prop)()],f.prototype,"story",void 0);var _=f=m([Object(o.Component)({})],f),w=(n(402),n(58)),y=n(79),x=n.n(y),v=n(323),k=n(304),N=n(330),S=n(414),A=n(395),component=Object(w.a)(_,(function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("div",{staticClass:"story"},[n("h6",{staticClass:"title"},[e._v(e._s(e.storyId))]),e._v(" "),n("div",{staticClass:"story__text-wrap",attrs:{id:e.storyId}},[n("p",{staticClass:"story__text",domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(e.text)}})]),e._v(" "),n("v-row",e._l(e.story.questions,(function(q,t){return n("v-col",{key:t,attrs:{cols:"12",md:"6"}},[n("v-card",{staticClass:"question",class:"class-"+q.class},[n("div",{staticClass:"font-size-16 font-weight-medium"},[2===q.class?n("span",[e._v("[BAD QUESTION] ")]):e._e(),e._v(e._s(q.question))]),e._v(" "),n("v-card-text",[n("div",[n("span",{staticClass:"subheading"},[e._v("Answer")]),e._v(" "),n("div",{staticClass:"mb-2"},[e._l(e.extractAns[t],(function(t,r){return n("v-chip",{key:r+t,attrs:{small:""},on:{click:function(n){return e.clickChip(t)}}},[e._v(e._s(t))])})),e._v(" "),e.extractAns[t].length?e._e():n("span",[e._v("N/A")])],2)]),e._v(" "),n("div",[n("span",{staticClass:"subheading"},[e._v("Prediction")]),e._v(" "),n("div",{staticClass:"mb-2"},[q.pred_ans?n("v-chip",{attrs:{small:""},on:{click:function(t){return e.clickChip(q.pred_ans,!0)}}},[e._v(e._s(q.pred_ans))]):n("span",[e._v("N/A")])],1)])])],1)],1)})),1)],1)}),[],!1,null,null,null),W=component.exports;x()(component,{VCard:v.a,VCardText:k.b,VChip:N.a,VCol:S.a,VRow:A.a});var T=function(e,t,n,desc){var r,o=arguments.length,d=o<3?t:null===desc?desc=Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(t,n):desc;if("object"==typeof Reflect&&"function"==typeof Reflect.decorate)d=Reflect.decorate(e,t,n,desc);else for(var i=e.length-1;i>=0;i--)(r=e[i])&&(d=(o<3?r(d):o>3?r(t,n,d):r(t,n))||d);return o>3&&d&&Object.defineProperty(t,n,d),d},z=function(e){function t(){var t;return(t=e.apply(this,arguments)||this).demoData=d,t}return Object(r.a)(t,e),t}(o.Vue),I=z=T([Object(o.Component)({components:{story:W}})],z),C=n(415),U=Object(w.a)(I,(function(){var e=this.$createElement,t=this._self._c||e;return t("v-container",{staticClass:"py-6"},[t("h3",{staticClass:"font-size-24 font-size-md-32 mb-7"},[this._v("News QA Dataset Demo")]),this._v(" "),this._l(this.demoData,(function(e){return t("story",{key:e.story_id,attrs:{story:e}})}))],2)}),[],!1,null,null,null);t.default=U.exports;x()(U,{VContainer:C.a})}}]);